<?xml version="1.0" ?><actors>
    <actor>
        <name>Alan Tudyk</name>
        <birthday>1971-03-16</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Alan Wray Tudyk (/ˈtuːdɪk/ TOO-dik; born March 16, 1971) is an American actor and voice actor known for his roles as Hoban "Wash" Washburne in the space western television series Firefly and movie Serenity, Alpha in the science fiction TV series Dollhouse, Tucker McGee in Tucker &amp; Dale vs. Evil, Steve the Pirate in DodgeBall: A True Underdog Story, and Wat in A Knight's Tale. He also co-starred on the ABC sitcom Suburgatory. Tudyk had a supporting role in the film 42 as baseball manager Ben Chapman and voiced roles in Walt Disney Animation Studios' Wreck-It Ralph, Frozen, Big Hero 6, Zootopia, and Moana. He has also featured in the web series Con Man and the films Maze Runner: The Scorch Trials and Rogue One: A Star Wars Story.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3748528</movie>
            <movie>tt5848272</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Khushi Solanki</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3741834</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jessica McNamee</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0493405</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Danai Gurira</name>
        <birthday>1978-02-14</birthday>
        <age>39</age>
        <biography>Danai Jekesai Gurira (born February 14, 1978) is an American actress and playwright of Zimbabwean ancestry, best known for her role as Michonne on The Walking Dead, an AMC television horror drama series, and as the writer of the Tony Award-winning play Eclipsed.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1666185</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Joe Pesci</name>
        <birthday>1943-02-09</birthday>
        <age>74</age>
        <biography>Joseph Frank "Joe" Pesci (/ˈpɛʃi/ PESH-ee; born February 9, 1943) is an American actor, singer, musician and comedian. Known for playing tough, volatile characters, in a variety of genres. He is best known for a trio of Martin Scorsese films in which he co-starred with Robert De Niro: Raging Bull (1980), Goodfellas (1990) and Casino (1995).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1302006</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Faye Dunaway</name>
        <birthday>1941-01-14</birthday>
        <age>76</age>
        <biography>Dorothy Faye Dunaway (born January 14, 1941) is an American actress. She has won an Academy Award, three Golden Globes, a BAFTA, an Emmy, and was the first-ever recipient of a Leopard Club Award that honors film professionals whose work has left a mark on the collective imagination. In 2011, the government of France made her an Officer of the Order of Arts and Letters.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6113488</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rhys Darby</name>
        <birthday>1974-03-21</birthday>
        <age>43</age>
        <biography>Rhys Montague Darby (born 21 March 1974)[2][3] is an actor and comedian from New Zealand, known for his energetic physical comedy routines, telling stories accompanied with mime and sound effects[4] of things such as machinery and animals.[5] He was nominated for the Billy T Award in 2001 and 2002.[6] He also won the 2012 Fred (Dagg) award at the New Zealand International Comedy Festival, for Best NZ show.[7]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2283362</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kevin Zegers</name>
        <birthday>1984-09-19</birthday>
        <age>33</age>
        <biography>Kevin Joseph Zegers (born September 19, 1984) is a Canadian actor and model. He is known for his roles as Alec Lightwood in The Mortal Instruments: City of Bones, Josh Framm in the Air Bud film series, and Damien Dalgaard in the CW teen drama Gossip Girl. He also starred in the films Dawn of the Dead (2004), Transamerica (2005), It's a Boy Girl Thing (2006), The Jane Austen Book Club (2007), Fifty Dead Men Walking (2008), and Frozen (2010).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4581576</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sam Worthington</name>
        <birthday>1976-08-02</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Samuel Henry John "Sam" Worthington[1] (born 2 August 1976) is an Australian actor. He played the main character role of Alex Mason in the Call of Duty: Black Ops series. He portrayed the protagonist Jake Sully in the 2009 film Avatar; Marcus Wright in Terminator Salvation; and Perseus in Clash of the Titans and its sequel, Wrath of the Titans; before transitioning to more dramatic roles, in Everest (2015) and Hacksaw Ridge (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2872518</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Lara Pulver</name>
        <birthday>1980-09-01</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Lara Pulver (born 1 September 1980) is an English actress. She has played Erin Watts in the British BBC spy drama Spooks, and Irene Adler on BBC's TV adaptation Sherlock. She won the 2016 Olivier Award for Best Supporting Actress in a Musical in the West End's revival of the hit Broadway musical Gypsy.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3717252</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sylvester Stallone</name>
        <birthday>1946-07-06</birthday>
        <age>71</age>
        <biography>Michael Sylvester Gardenzio Stallone[1][2][3][4][5][6][7] (/stəˈloʊn/; Italian: [stalˈloːne]; born July 6, 1946) is an American actor, filmmaker, and screenwriter. He is well known for his Hollywood action roles, including boxer Rocky Balboa, the title character of the Rocky series' seven films from 1976 to 2015; soldier John Rambo from the four Rambo films, released between 1982 and 2008; and Barney Ross in the three The Expendables films from 2010 to 2014. He wrote or co-wrote most of the 14 films in all three franchises, and directed many of the films.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6513656</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rooney Mara</name>
        <birthday>1985-04-17</birthday>
        <age>32</age>
        <biography>Patricia Rooney Mara (/ˈmɛərə/ MAIR-ə;[2] born April 17, 1985)[1] is an American actress and philanthropist. She made her screen debut in the slasher film Urban Legends: Bloody Mary (2005) and went on to have a breakout role in the independent coming-of-age drama Tanner Hall (2009), followed by roles in the 2010 remake of A Nightmare on Elm Street and the biographical drama film The Social Network (2010).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6288124</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Adam David Thompson</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4814760</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kit Harington</name>
        <birthday>1986-12-26</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Christopher Catesby "Kit" Harington (born 26 December 1986) is an English actor. He rose to prominence playing the role of Jon Snow in the HBO television series Game of Thrones (2011–present), which garnered him a nomination for the 2016 Primetime Emmy Award. In 2017, Harington became one of the highest paid actors on television and earned US$1.1 million per episode of Game of Thrones.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1895315</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Pom Klementieff</name>
        <birthday>1986-05-03</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Pom Klementieff (born 3 May 1986) is a Canadian-born French actress. She was trained at the Cours Florent drama school in Paris and has appeared in such films as Loup (2009), Sleepless Night (2011) and Hacker's Game (2015). She portrays the role of Mantis in the upcoming film Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2 (2017).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3896198</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Justin Timberlake</name>
        <birthday>1981-01-31</birthday>
        <age>36</age>
        <biography>Justin Randall Timberlake (born January 31, 1981)[2] is an American singer-songwriter, actor and record producer. Born and raised in Tennessee, he appeared on the television shows Star Search and The All-New Mickey Mouse Club as a child. In the late 1990s, Timberlake rose to prominence as one of the two lead vocalists and youngest member of NSYNC, which eventually became one of the best-selling boy bands of all time. Timberlake began to adopt a more mature image as an artist with the release of his debut solo album, the R&amp;B-focused Justified (2002), which yielded the successful singles "Cry Me a River" and "Rock Your Body", and earned his first two Grammy Awards.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1679335</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bingbing Li</name>
        <birthday>1973-02-27</birthday>
        <age>44</age>
        <biography>Li Bingbing (born February 27, 1973) is a Chinese actress and singer. She rose to fame with her role in Seventeen Years (1999) and since then received critical acclaim for her roles in A World Without Thieves (2004), Waiting Alone (2005), The Knot (2006), The Forbidden Kingdom (2008), The Message (2009), Detective Dee and the Mystery of the Phantom Flame (2010) and Zhong Kui: Snow Girl and the Dark Crystal (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4779682</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jenny Slate</name>
        <birthday>1982-03-25</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Jennifer Sarah "Jenny" Slate (born March 25, 1982) is an American comedian, actress, voice actress and author, best known for her role as Donna Stern in Obvious Child, as well as being the co-creator of the Marcel the Shell with Shoes On short films and children's book series. She is also known for being a cast member on Saturday Night Live for the 2009/10 season and for her appearances in shows such as House of Lies, Married, Parks and Recreation, Bob's Burgers, Hello Ladies, Kroll Show, and Girls.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4481414</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Elle Fanning</name>
        <birthday>1998-04-09</birthday>
        <age>19</age>
        <biography>Mary Elle Fanning (born April 9, 1998) is an American actress. She is the younger sister of actress Dakota Fanning.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2361317</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tom Hiddleston</name>
        <birthday>1981-02-09</birthday>
        <age>36</age>
        <biography>Thomas William "Tom" Hiddleston (born 9 February 1981)[1] is an English actor, producer and musical performer. At the beginning of his career, he appeared in West End theatre productions of Cymbeline (2007) and Ivanov (2008). He won the Laurence Olivier Award for Best Newcomer in a Play for his role in Cymbeline and was also nominated for the same award for his role as Cassio in Othello.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3731562</movie>
            <movie>tt3501632</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Brie Larson</name>
        <birthday>1989-10-01</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Brianne Sidonie Desaulniers (born October 1, 1989),[1] known professionally as Brie Larson, is an American actress, director, and singer. Born in Sacramento, California, Larson was home-schooled before she studied acting at the American Conservatory Theater. She began her acting career in television, appearing as a regular on the 2001 sitcom Raising Dad, for which she was nominated for a Young Artist Award.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4158096</movie>
            <movie>tt3731562</movie>
            <movie>tt4154756</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Woody Harrelson</name>
        <birthday>1961-07-23</birthday>
        <age>56</age>
        <biography>Woodrow Tracy "Woody" Harrelson[1][2] (born July 23, 1961)[3] is an American actor, activist and playwright. He is a two-time Academy Award nominee and has won one Emmy Award out of seven nominations. His breakout role came in 1985, joining the television sitcom Cheers as bartender Woody Boyd, for which he earned five Emmy Award nominations (one win). Some notable film characters include basketball hustler Billy Hoyle in White Men Can't Jump, one-handed bowler Roy Munson in Kingpin, Haymitch Abernathy in The Hunger Games film series, Pepper Lewis in The Cowboy Way, Tallahassee in Zombieland, serial killer Mickey Knox in Natural Born Killers, magazine publisher Larry Flynt in The People vs. Larry Flynt, country singer Dusty in A Prairie Home Companion, and magician/mentalist Merritt McKinney in Now You See Me. He will be portraying the Colonel in War for the Planet of the Apes.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3450958</movie>
            <movie>tt3778644</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Idris Elba</name>
        <birthday>1972-09-06</birthday>
        <age>45</age>
        <biography>Idrissa Akuna "Idris" Elba, OBE (/ˈɪdrᵻs ˈɛlbə/; born 6 September 1972)[2] is an English actor, musician, and DJ.[3][4] He is known for playing druglord Russell "Stringer" Bell on the HBO series The Wire,[5] Detective John Luther on the BBC One series Luther, and Nelson Mandela in the biographical film Mandela: Long Walk to Freedom (2013). He has been nominated four times for a Golden Globe Award for Best Actor in a Miniseries or Television Film, winning one, and was nominated five times for a Primetime Emmy Award.[6][7]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3501632</movie>
            <movie>tt1648190</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rhet Kidd</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4572514</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Emma Watson</name>
        <birthday>1990-04-15</birthday>
        <age>27</age>
        <biography>Emma Charlotte Duerre Watson (born 15 April 1990)[4] is a British actress, model, and activist. Born in Paris and brought up in Oxfordshire, Watson attended the Dragon School and trained as an actress at the Oxford branch of Stagecoach Theatre Arts. She rose to prominence after landing her first professional acting role as Hermione Granger in the Harry Potter film series, having acted only in school plays previously.[5] Watson appeared in all eight Harry Potter films from 2001 to 2011, earning worldwide fame, critical accolades, and around $60 million.[6]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2771200</movie>
            <movie>tt4287320</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Milla Jovovich</name>
        <birthday>1975-12-17</birthday>
        <age>42</age>
        <biography>Milica Bogdanovna "Milla" Jovovich[nb 1][nb 2] (/ˈjoʊvəvɪtʃ/ YOH-və-vich; born December 17, 1975) is an American actress, model, musician, and fashion designer. She has appeared in numerous science fiction and action films, leading the music channel VH1 to deem her the "reigning queen of kick-butt" in 2006.[2] In 2004, she was the highest-paid model in the world according to Forbes.[3]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2592614</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Alexandra Daddario</name>
        <birthday>1986-03-16</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Alexandra Anna Daddario[1] (born March 16, 1986) is an American actress. She is best known for playing Annabeth Chase in the Percy Jackson film series, and Blake Gaines in San Andreas. She starred in the films Texas Chainsaw 3D and Hall Pass, and has guest starred on series including White Collar, It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia, True Detective, and American Horror Story: Hotel.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1469304</movie>
            <movie>tt6533240</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tom Holland</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1212428</movie>
            <movie>tt2250912</movie>
            <movie>tt4154756</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Susan Sarandon</name>
        <birthday>1946-10-04</birthday>
        <age>71</age>
        <biography>Susan Abigail Sarandon (/səˈrændən/; née Tomalin; born October 4, 1946)[1] is an American actress and activist. She is an Academy Award and BAFTA Award winner who is also known for her social and political activism for a variety of causes. She was appointed a UNICEF Goodwill Ambassador in 1999 and received the Action Against Hunger Humanitarian Award in 2006.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4042818</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jeremy Irons</name>
        <birthday>1948-09-19</birthday>
        <age>69</age>
        <biography>Jeremy John Irons (born 19 September 1948)[1] is an English actor. After receiving classical training at the Bristol Old Vic Theatre School, Irons began his acting career on stage in 1969 and has since appeared in many West End theatre productions, including The Winter's Tale, Macbeth, Much Ado About Nothing, The Taming of the Shrew, Godspell, Richard II, and Embers. In 1984, he made his Broadway debut in Tom Stoppard's The Real Thing and received a Tony Award for Best Actor.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2094766</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Gael García Bernal</name>
        <birthday>1978-10-30</birthday>
        <age>39</age>
        <biography>Gael García Bernal (Spanish pronunciation: [ɡaˈel ɣarˈsi.a βerˈnal]; born 30 October 1978) is a Mexican film actor, director, and producer. He and Diego Luna founded Canana Films in Mexico City. He is mostly known for his performances in the films Bad Education, The Motorcycle Diaries, and Babel, and in Amazon Studios' web television series Mozart in the Jungle.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4441150</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Charlie Day</name>
        <birthday>1976-02-09</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Charles Peckham "Charlie" Day (born February 9, 1976)[1] is an American actor, screenwriter, producer, comedian, and musician. He is best known for playing Charlie Kelly on It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia.[2] On film, he is known for his role as Dale in the films Horrible Bosses (2011) and its 2014 sequel, as well as for his roles in Monsters University (2013), Pacific Rim (2013), The Lego Movie (2014) and Fist Fight (2017).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2557478</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Chiwetel Ejiofor</name>
        <birthday>1977-07-10</birthday>
        <age>40</age>
        <biography>Chiwetel Umeadi Ejiofor,[3] CBE, (/ˈtʃuːwᵻtɛl ˈɛdʒi.oʊfɔːr/ CHEW-i-tel EJ-i-oh-for; born 10 July 1977)[3][4] is a British actor.[5] After enrolling at the National Youth Theatre in 1995, and gaining a scholarship to the London Academy of Music and Dramatic Art, at age 19 and three months into his course, Ejiofor was cast by Steven Spielberg to play a supporting part in the film Amistad as James Covey.[6]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1211837</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ben Skelton</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2763304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jared Leto</name>
        <birthday>1971-12-26</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Jared Joseph Leto (/ˈlɛtoʊ/; born December 26, 1971) is an American actor, singer-songwriter, and director. After starting his career with television appearances in the early 1990s, Leto achieved recognition for his role as Jordan Catalano on the television series My So-Called Life (1994). He made his film debut in How to Make an American Quilt (1995) and received critical praise for his performance in Prefontaine (1997). Leto played supporting roles in The Thin Red Line (1998), Fight Club (1999) and American Psycho (2000), as well as the lead role in Urban Legend (1998), and earned critical acclaim after portraying heroin addict Harry Goldfarb in Requiem for a Dream (2000). He later began focusing increasingly on his music career, returning to acting with Panic Room (2002), Alexander (2004), Lord of War (2005), Lonely Hearts (2006), Chapter 27 (2007), and Mr. Nobody (2009). In 2012, he directed the documentary film Artifact. In 2016, he played the DC Comics supervillain Joker in the DC Extended Universe film Suicide Squad.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1856101</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Gary Oldman</name>
        <birthday>1958-03-21</birthday>
        <age>59</age>
        <biography>Gary Leonard Oldman[1] (born 21 March 1958)[2] is an English actor, filmmaker, musician and author who has performed in theatre, film and television. He is known for his "big" acting style and on-screen diversity.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3922818</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Betty Buckley</name>
        <birthday>1947-07-03</birthday>
        <age>70</age>
        <biography>Betty Lynn Buckley (born July 3, 1947) is an American stage, film and television actress, and singer. She starred from 1977 to 1981 on the ABC series Eight is Enough, before going on to win the 1983 Tony Award for Best Featured Actress in a Musical for her role as Grizabella in the original Broadway production of Cats. Her other musical roles include playing Norma Desmond in Sunset Boulevard from 1994 to 1996, in both London and New York, receiving an Olivier Award nomination. She is a 2012 American Theater Hall of Fame inductee.[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4972582</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sam Redford</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3183660</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Terry Walters</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3783958</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Felicity Jones</name>
        <birthday>1983-10-17</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Felicity Rose Hadley Jones (born 17 October 1983)[1] is an English actress. She started her professional acting career as a child, appearing at age 12 in The Treasure Seekers (1996). Jones went on to play Ethel Hallow for one season in the television show The Worst Witch and its sequel Weirdsister College. She took time off from acting to attend university at Wadham College, Oxford where she performed in Shakespeare's The Comedy of Errors for the Oxford University Dramatic Society, and has worked steadily since graduating in 2006. On radio, she has played the role of Emma Grundy in the BBC's The Archers. In 2008, she appeared in the Donmar Warehouse production of The Chalk Garden.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3748528</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Natalie Portman</name>
        <birthday>1981-06-09</birthday>
        <age>36</age>
        <biography>Natalie Portman (born Neta-Lee Hershlag, Hebrew: נטע-לי הרשלג‎‎;[3] June 9, 1981[4]) is an actress with dual American and Israeli citizenship. Her first role was in the 1994 action thriller Léon: The Professional, opposite Jean Reno. She was later cast as Padmé Amidala in the Star Wars prequel trilogy (released in 1999, 2002 and 2005).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4042818</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jennifer Jason Leigh</name>
        <birthday>1962-02-05</birthday>
        <age>55</age>
        <biography>Jennifer Jason Leigh (born Jennifer Leigh Morrow on February 5, 1962) is an American actress and producer. Leigh began her career as a teenager in the 1970s, guest-starring on several television shows. Her film breakthrough came in 1982 for her performance as Stacy Hamilton in Fast Times at Ridgemont High. Leigh continued performing past her teen years, receiving critical praise for her roles in the 1990 films Miami Blues and Last Exit to Brooklyn. In 1991, she appeared in Ron Howard's Backdraft, and in 1992 she acted in the drama-thriller Single White Female.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4537896</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Shannon</name>
        <birthday>1974-08-07</birthday>
        <age>43</age>
        <biography>Michael Corbett Shannon (born August 7, 1974)[1][2] is an American actor and musician. He made his film debut opposite Bill Murray in Groundhog Day (1993) and received widespread attention for his performance in 8 Mile (2002), where he portrayed the boyfriend of Eminem's character's mother (Kim Basinger). Shannon is known for his on-screen versatility, performing in both comedies and dramas. Notable projects include Pearl Harbor (2001), Bad Boys II (2003), Bug (2006), Before the Devil Knows You're Dead (2007), The Iceman (2012), Man of Steel (2013) and Elvis &amp; Nixon (2016). He is a frequent collaborator with Jeff Nichols, appearing in all of his films: Shotgun Stories (2007), Take Shelter (2011), Mud (2012), Midnight Special and Loving (both 2016). He is also known for his role as Nelson Van Alden/George Mueller in the HBO period drama series Boardwalk Empire (2010–2014).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4550098</movie>
            <movie>tt4441150</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Laurent Lucas</name>
        <birthday>1965-07-20</birthday>
        <age>52</age>
        <biography>Laurent Lucas (born 20 July 1965) is a French actor.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4954522</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Vincent Ebrahim</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3640424</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jesse Eisenberg</name>
        <birthday>1983-10-05</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Jesse Adam Eisenberg (born October 5, 1983) is an American actor, author and playwright. Born and raised in New York City, Eisenberg began acting in plays at an early age, and made his television debut with the short-lived comedy-drama series Get Real (1999–2000). Following his first leading role in the comedy-drama film Roger Dodger (2002), he appeared in the drama film The Emperor's Club (2002), the psychological thriller film The Village (2004), the comedy-drama film The Squid and the Whale (2005) and the drama film The Education of Charlie Banks (2007). In 2006, Eisenberg won the Vail Film Festival Rising Star Award for his role in The Living Wake.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2975590</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Anna Kendrick</name>
        <birthday>1985-08-09</birthday>
        <age>32</age>
        <biography>Anna Cooke Kendrick (born August 9, 1985) is an American actress and singer. She began her career as a child actor in theater productions. Her first prominent role was in the 1998 Broadway musical High Society, which earned her a Tony Award nomination for Best Featured Actress in a Musical. She made her film debut in the musical comedy Camp (2003).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1679335</movie>
            <movie>tt2140479</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>N/A</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3829266</movie>
            <movie>tt4566758</movie>
            <movie>tt5814060</movie>
            <movie>tt1270797</movie>
            <movie>tt4073790</movie>
            <movie>tt5619332</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Catherine Keener</name>
        <birthday>1959-03-23</birthday>
        <age>58</age>
        <biography>Catherine Ann Keener (born March 23, 1959)[2] is an American actress. She has been twice nominated for the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress for her roles as Maxine Lund in Being John Malkovich (1999) and Harper Lee in Capote (2005). Keener also appeared in the films Into the Wild (2007) and Synecdoche, New York (2008), which were well received by critics. Keener is also the noted muse of director Nicole Holofcener, having appeared in every work of hers to date.[3]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5052448</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Robert Forster</name>
        <birthday>1941-07-13</birthday>
        <age>76</age>
        <biography>Robert Wallace Forster, Jr. (born July 13, 1941) is an American actor. He is best known for his roles as news cameraman John Cassellis in Haskell Wexler's Medium Cool (1969), Lebanese terrorist Abdul Rafai in the action-thriller The Delta Force (1986) and bail bondsman Max Cherry in Quentin Tarantino's Jackie Brown (1997), the last of which saw him nominated for the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6113488</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Christopher Mintz-Plasse</name>
        <birthday>1989-06-20</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Christopher Mintz-Plasse (/mɪnts ˈplæs/; born June 20, 1989)[1] is an American actor and musician who has performed roles such as Fogell (better known as "McLovin") in Superbad, Augie Farcques in Role Models, and as Chris D'Amico in Kick-Ass and its sequel Kick-Ass 2.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1679335</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sarah Vowell</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3606756</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Joaquin Phoenix</name>
        <birthday>1974-10-28</birthday>
        <age>43</age>
        <biography>Joaquín Rafael Phoenix (/ˌhwɑːˈkiːn/; born Joaquín Rafael Bottom; October 28, 1974), known formerly as Leaf Phoenix,[1] is a Puerto Rican–born American actor, producer, music video director, musician and activist. For his work as an artist, Phoenix has received a Grammy Award, a Golden Globe Award and three Academy Award nominations.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6288124</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Martin Lawrence</name>
        <birthday>1965-04-16</birthday>
        <age>52</age>
        <biography>Martin Fitzgerald Lawrence[1] (born April 16, 1965) is a German-born American stand-up comedian, actor, producer, writer, and voice actor. Lawrence came to fame during the 1990s, establishing a Hollywood career as a leading actor, most notably in the television sitcom Martin and the films House Party, Boomerang, Bad Boys, Wild Hogs, Nothing to Lose, Blue Streak, Life, Big Momma's House, and A Thin Line Between Love &amp; Hate.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1502397</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Margot Robbie</name>
        <birthday>1990-07-02</birthday>
        <age>27</age>
        <biography>Margot Elise Robbie (/ˈmɑːrɡoʊ ˈrɒbi/; born 2 July 1990)[1][2][3] is an Australian actress. Robbie started her career by appearing in Australian independent films in the late 2000s. She was later cast in the soap opera Neighbours (2008–2011), which earned her two Logie Award nominations.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1386697</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Adam Driver</name>
        <birthday>1983-11-19</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Adam Douglas Driver[1] (born November 19, 1983) is an American actor. He rose to prominence in the supporting role of Adam Sackler in the HBO comedy-drama series Girls (2012–2017), for which he received three consecutive nominations for the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Comedy Series. He made his Broadway debut in Mrs. Warren's Profession (2010). In 2011, he returned to Broadway in Man and Boy and made his feature film debut in J. Edgar.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0490215</movie>
            <movie>tt2527336</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Xavier De Guillebon</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3640424</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Doug Jones</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4030600</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Henry Cavill</name>
        <birthday>1983-05-05</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Henry William Dalgliesh Cavill (/ˈkævᵻl/; born 5 May 1983) is a British actor.[2][3][4][5] Cavill began his career starring in the film adaptations of The Count of Monte Cristo (2002) and I Capture the Castle (2003). He later appeared in minor and supporting roles in television shows such as BBC's The Inspector Lynley Mysteries, ITV's Midsomer Murders and Showtime's The Tudors (2007-10), then crossed to mainstream Hollywood films such as Tristan &amp; Isolde (2006), Stardust (2007), Blood Creek (2009) and Immortals (2011).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2975590</movie>
            <movie>tt0974015</movie>
            <movie>tt6533240</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Will Smith</name>
        <birthday>1968-09-15</birthday>
        <age>49</age>
        <biography>Willard Carroll "Will" Smith Jr. (born September 15, 1968) is an American actor, producer, rapper, and songwriter. In April 2007, Newsweek called him "the most powerful actor in Hollywood".[2] Smith has been nominated for five Golden Globe Awards and two Academy Awards, and has won four Grammy Awards.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1386697</movie>
            <movie>tt4682786</movie>
            <movie>tt1502397</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>J.K. Simmons</name>
        <birthday>1955-01-09</birthday>
        <age>62</age>
        <biography>Jonathan Kimble "J. K." Simmons (born January 9, 1955) is an American actor and voice actor. In television, he is known for playing Dr. Emil Skoda on the NBC series Law &amp; Order (and other Law &amp; Order franchise series), neo-Nazi Vernon Schillinger on the HBO prison-drama Oz, and Assistant Police Chief Will Pope on TNT's The Closer. His film roles include J. Jonah Jameson in Sam Raimi's Spider-Man trilogy and music instructor Terence Fletcher in 2014's Whiplash. He is also known for voicing Cave Johnson in the video game Portal 2 (2011), Tenzin in The Legend of Korra (2012), Stanford Pines in Gravity Falls, Kai in Kung Fu Panda 3 (2016), and Mayor Lionheart in Zootopia (2016). Simmons also reprised his role as J. Jonah Jameson in various Marvel animated series and video games. He has also appeared in a series of television commercials for Farmers Insurance.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2140479</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Temuera Morrison</name>
        <birthday>1960-12-26</birthday>
        <age>57</age>
        <biography>Temuera Derek Morrison MNZM (born 26 December 1960) is a New Zealand actor, first gained recognition for his role as Dr. Hone Ropata on the New Zealand soap opera Shortland Street and first gained critical acclaim after starring as Jake "The Muss" Heke in the 1994 film Once Were Warriors and its 1999 sequel What Becomes of the Broken Hearted?.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3521164</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Mark Hamill</name>
        <birthday>1951-09-25</birthday>
        <age>66</age>
        <biography>Mark Richard Hamill (born September 25, 1951) is an American actor, voice actor, producer and writer. He is known for playing Luke Skywalker in the Star Wars film series. His other works include Corvette Summer (1978) and The Big Red One (1980), among other television shows and movies. Hamill has also appeared on stage in several theater productions, primarily during the 1980s. He currently recurs in the The CW television series The Flash as James Jesse / Trickster, a role he previously portrayed in the CBS's television series The Flash.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2527336</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Armie Hammer</name>
        <birthday>1986-08-28</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Armand Douglas "Armie" Hammer (born August 28, 1986)[1] is an American actor. He is known for his portrayal of the Winklevoss twins in the film The Social Network (2010), Prince Andrew Alcott in Mirror Mirror (2012), the title character in the adventure film The Lone Ranger (2013), and Mike in Mine (2016). He played the role of Illya Kuryakin in The Man from U.N.C.L.E. (2015), and stars as Oliver in the 2017 romance drama Call Me by Your Name. For his portrayal of Clyde Tolson in J. Edgar (2011), he was nominated for a Screen Actors Guild Award.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3707104</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Laurence Fishburne</name>
        <birthday>1961-07-30</birthday>
        <age>56</age>
        <biography>Laurence John Fishburne III[1] (born July 30, 1961) is an American actor, playwright, director and producer, best known for playing Morpheus in The Matrix trilogy, Jason "Furious" Styles in the 1991 drama film Boyz n the Hood and Tyrone "Mr. Clean" Miller in the 1979 war film Apocalypse Now.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1355644</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jeff Goldblum</name>
        <birthday>1952-10-22</birthday>
        <age>65</age>
        <biography>Jeffrey Lynn "Jeff" Goldblum (/ˈɡoʊldbluːm/; born October 22, 1952) is an American actor who has received nominations for an Oscar, an Emmy, a Genie and a Drama Desk Award throughout his career and is best known for starring in the highest-grossing films of his era, Jurassic Park (1993) and Independence Day (1996), as well as their respective sequels, The Lost World: Jurassic Park (1997) and Independence Day: Resurgence (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5104604</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rebecca Ferguson</name>
        <birthday>1983-10-19</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Rebecca Louisa Ferguson Sundström[1] (born 19 October 1983), known professionally as Rebecca Ferguson, is a Swedish actress.[2] She is best known for her lead role as Elizabeth Woodville in The White Queen (2013), which earned her a Golden Globe nomination, and her starring role as Ilsa Faust in Mission: Impossible – Rogue Nation (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3631112</movie>
            <movie>tt5442430</movie>
            <movie>tt4912910</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Anita Briem</name>
        <birthday>1982-05-29</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Anita Briem (born 29 May 1982) is an Icelandic actress. She is known for her role as Jane Seymour on The Tudors and her role as Hannah Ásgeirsdottir in Journey to the Center of the Earth.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4441150</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Benedict Wong</name>
        <birthday>1971-06-03</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Benedict Wong (born 3 June 1971) is an English actor. He has appeared on film, television, and also on stage. Wong is best known for portraying Kublai Khan in Netflix's Marco Polo (2014-2016), Bruce Ng in The Martian (2015) and Wong in Marvel's film adaptation of Doctor Strange (2016), and will reprise that role in Avengers: Infinity War (2018).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1211837</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Werner Herzog</name>
        <birthday>1942-09-05</birthday>
        <age>75</age>
        <biography>Werner Herzog[1] (German: [ˈvɛɐ̯nɐ ˈhɛɐ̯tsoːk]; born 5 September 1942) is a German screenwriter, film director, author, actor, and opera director.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4441150</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Emilia Clarke</name>
        <birthday>1986-10-23</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Emilia Clarke (born 23 October 1986)[1][2] is an English actress. Brought up in Berkshire, she first gained an interest in acting as a child after seeing the musical Show Boat, on which her father was working as a sound engineer. She was educated at Rye St Antony School, Headington and graduated from secondary school at St. Edward's in Oxford, where she appeared in two plays, before studying at the Drama Centre London, where she graduated from in 2009, and appeared in ten different stage productions. Some of her earliest work following graduation included a role in a play by the Company of Angels, two commercials for Samaritans, and a University of London students' short film. Her television debut came with a guest appearance in an episode of the British soap opera Doctors and she was named as one of the UK Stars of Tomorrow by Screen International magazine for her role in Syfy's film Triassic Attack (2010).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3778644</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Charlie Hunnam</name>
        <birthday>1980-04-10</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Charles Matthew Hunnam (born 10 April 1980)[1] is an English actor. He is known for his roles as Jackson "Jax" Teller in the FX drama series Sons of Anarchy (2008–14), Nathan Maloney in the Channel 4 drama Queer as Folk (1999–2000), Lloyd Haythe in the Fox comedy series Undeclared (2001–02), the title role in Nicholas Nickleby (2002), Pete Dunham in Green Street (2005), and Raleigh Becket in Pacific Rim (2013).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1212428</movie>
            <movie>tt1972591</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Iain Glen</name>
        <birthday>1961-06-24</birthday>
        <age>56</age>
        <biography>Iain Glen (born 24 June 1961) is a Scottish film, television, and stage actor.[1] Glen is best known for his roles as Dr. Alexander Isaacs / Tyrant in the Resident Evil films and for portraying Ser Jorah Mormont on Game of Thrones. Other notable roles include John Hanning Speke in Mountains of the Moon, Sir Richard Carlisle in Downton Abbey, the title role in Jack Taylor and Jarrod Slade in Cleverman.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2592614</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Anne Hathaway</name>
        <birthday>1982-11-12</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Anne Jacqueline Hathaway (born November 12, 1982) is an American actress and singer. Born in Brooklyn, New York and brought up in Millburn, New Jersey, Hathaway was inspired to act by her mother and as a high school student was nominated for the Paper Mill Playhouse Rising Star Award for Best Performance by a High School Actress for her performance in Once Upon a Mattress. She made her professional screen debut in the short-lived Fox television series Get Real (1999–2000), before landing the lead role of Mia Thermopolis in the Disney comedy film The Princess Diaries (2001), for which she won the Teen Choice Award for Choice Movie Actress – Comedy. Hathaway went on to become a widely praised "role model for children" for her roles in Nicholas Nickleby (2002), Ella Enchanted (2004), The Princess Diaries 2: Royal Engagement (2004), and Hoodwinked! (2005).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4680182</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jennifer Lawrence</name>
        <birthday>1990-08-15</birthday>
        <age>27</age>
        <biography>Jennifer Shrader Lawrence (born August 15, 1990) is an American actress. Since 2015, Lawrence has been the highest-paid actress in the world, and her films have grossed over $5 billion worldwide. She appeared in Time's 100 most influential people in the world in 2013 and Forbes Celebrity 100 the following year and in 2016.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1355644</movie>
            <movie>tt3385516</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Enzo Cilenti</name>
        <birthday>1974-08-08</birthday>
        <age>43</age>
        <biography>Vincenzo Leonardo "Enzo" Cilenti (born 8 August 1974) is an English actor, known for his roles in works such as The Theory of Everything, Guardians of the Galaxy, Jonathan Strange &amp; Mr Norrell, and Game of Thrones.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4158096</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>James Franco</name>
        <birthday>1978-04-19</birthday>
        <age>39</age>
        <biography>James Edward Franco (born April 19, 1978)[2] is an American actor and filmmaker known for his work in both comedic and dramatic films and TV shows. For his role in 127 Hours (2010), Franco was nominated for an Academy Award for Best Actor. He is known for his roles in live-action films such as Milk (2008), Pineapple Express (2008), Rise of the Planet of the Apes (2011), Spring Breakers (2012), Oz the Great and Powerful (2013), This Is the End (2013), Goat (2016), and Sam Raimi's Spider-Man trilogy, while also voicing characters in the animated films The Little Prince (2015) and Sausage Party (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4501244</movie>
            <movie>tt2316204</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sophie Turner</name>
        <birthday>1996-02-21</birthday>
        <age>21</age>
        <biography>Sophie Turner (born 21 February 1996)[1] is an English actress. Turner made her professional acting debut as Sansa Stark on the HBO fantasy television series Game of Thrones (2011–present), which brought her international recognition and critical praise. For her performance, she has received four nominations for Screen Actors Guild Award for Outstanding Performance by an Ensemble in a Drama Series, as well as a Young Artist Award nomination for Best Supporting Young Actress in a TV Series.[2]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6565702</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Shawn Roberts</name>
        <birthday>1984-04-02</birthday>
        <age>33</age>
        <biography>Shawn Roberts (born April 2, 1984) is a Canadian actor. He is best known for his roles in zombie films such as Land of the Dead, Diary of the Dead, and the Resident Evil franchise.[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2592614</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jason Statham</name>
        <birthday>1967-07-26</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Jason Statham (/ˈsteɪθəm/ STAY-thəm;[citation needed] born 26 July 1967)[1][2] is an English actor and former model and competitive diver.[3]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4779682</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rich Moore</name>
        <birthday>1963-05-10</birthday>
        <age>54</age>
        <biography>Rich Moore (born May 10, 1963) is an American film and television animation director, voice actor, and a creative partner at both Rough Draft Studios and Walt Disney Animation Studios. He is best known[according to whom?] for his work on the animated television shows The Simpsons, The Critic, and Futurama, and for directing the Disney animated film Wreck-It Ralph (2012) and co-directing Zootopia (2016). He is a two-time Emmy Award winner, a three-time Annie Award winner, and an Academy Award winner.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5848272</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Marchand</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4572514</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Naomie Harris</name>
        <birthday>1976-09-06</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Naomie Melanie Harris,[1] OBE (born 6 September 1976)[1] is an English actress. She started her career as a child actress, appearing on the children television series Simon and the Witch in 1987. She played voodoo witch Tia Dalma in the second and third Pirates of the Caribbean films, Selena in 28 Days Later, and Winnie Mandela in Mandela: Long Walk to Freedom. She played Eve Moneypenny in the James Bond films Skyfall and Spectre. In 2016, she starred in the critically acclaimed film Moonlight; a performance which earned her several nominations for Best Supporting Actress awards, including the Golden Globe, BAFTA, and the Academy Award.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2231461</movie>
            <movie>tt2388771</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Garance Marillier</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4954522</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bill Skarsgård</name>
        <birthday>1990-08-09</birthday>
        <age>27</age>
        <biography>Bill Istvan Günther Skarsgård (born 9 August 1990) is a Swedish actor, known for his roles in Simple Simon, Allegiant, It, and Hemlock Grove.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1396484</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jake Gyllenhaal</name>
        <birthday>1980-12-19</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Jacob Benjamin "Jake" Gyllenhaal (/ˈdʒɪlənhɑːl/ JIL-ən-hahl;[1] born December 19, 1980) is an American actor. A member of the Gyllenhaal family and the son of director Stephen Gyllenhaal and screenwriter Naomi Foner, Gyllenhaal began acting as a child with a screen debut in City Slickers (1991), followed by roles in A Dangerous Woman (1993) and Homegrown (1998). His breakthrough performance was as Homer Hickam in October Sky (1999) and he garnered an Independent Spirit Award nomination for Best Male Lead for playing the title character in the indie cult hit Donnie Darko (2001), in which he played a psychologically troubled teenager alongside his older sister, Maggie Gyllenhaal. He subsequently appeared in another indie film, The Good Girl (2002) and the climate fiction-disaster film The Day After Tomorrow (2004), portraying a student caught in a cataclysmic climate event.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4550098</movie>
            <movie>tt5442430</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jamie Dornan</name>
        <birthday>1982-05-01</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>James "Jamie" Dornan (born 1 May 1982)[2][3] is a Northern Irish actor, model, and musician. He played Axel von Fersen in Sofia Coppola's film Marie Antoinette (2006), Sheriff Graham Humbert in the ABC series Once Upon a Time, serial killer Paul Spector in the BBC Two and RTÉ One crime drama series The Fall, and Christian Grey in the Fifty Shades franchise (2015-).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4465564</movie>
            <movie>tt4532826</movie>
            <movie>tt4477536</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Shariff Earp</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4975722</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Brad Pitt</name>
        <birthday>1963-12-18</birthday>
        <age>54</age>
        <biography>William Bradley "Brad" Pitt (born December 18, 1963) is an American actor and producer. He has received multiple awards and nominations including an Academy Award as producer under his own company Plan B Entertainment.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3640424</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dylan Minnette</name>
        <birthday>1996-12-29</birthday>
        <age>21</age>
        <biography>Dylan Christopher Minnette (born December 29, 1996) is an American actor and musician. He is known for his roles as Clay Jensen in 13 Reasons Why, David Shephard in Lost, Rex Britten in Awake, Anthony in Alexander and the Terrible, Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Day, Zach Cooper in Goosebumps, Jerry Fitzgerald Jr. in Scandal, and Alex in Don't Breathe.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4160708</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Annabelle Wallis</name>
        <birthday>1984-09-25</birthday>
        <age>33</age>
        <biography>Annabelle Wallis (born 25 September 1984) is an English actress best known for her roles as Jane Seymour in Showtime's period drama The Tudors (2009–10), Bridget in ABC's drama Pan Am (2011), Mia Form in the supernatural horror film Annabelle (2014) and as Grace Burgess in the BBC drama Peaky Blinders (2013–2016).[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3707104</movie>
            <movie>tt2345759</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rainn Wilson</name>
        <birthday>1966-01-20</birthday>
        <age>51</age>
        <biography>Rainn Dietrich Wilson /reɪn ˈdiːtrɪk ˈwɪlsən/[1] (born January 20, 1966) is an American actor, comedian, writer, director, and producer. He is best known for his role as Dwight Schrute on the American version of the television comedy The Office.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2398241</movie>
            <movie>tt4779682</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Maggie Grace</name>
        <birthday>1983-09-21</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Maggie Grace (born Margaret Grace Denig; September 21, 1983) is an American actress, best known for her roles as Shannon Rutherford on the ABC television series Lost and Kim Mills in the Taken trilogy. Originally from Worthington, Ohio, she dropped out of high school to move to Los Angeles with her mother after her parents' divorce. While struggling financially, she landed her first role as the title character in the web-based video series Rachel's Room in 2001. She went on to earn a Young Artist Award nomination in 2002 with her portrayal of 15-year-old murder victim Martha Moxley in the television movie Murder in Greenwich. In 2004, Grace was cast as Shannon Rutherford in the television series Lost, on which she was a main cast member for the first two seasons, winning a Screen Actors Guild Award shared with the ensemble cast. Leaving the series, Grace was keen to work more prominently in film, having starred opposite Tom Welling in The Fog in 2005. She appeared in Suburban Girl, The Jane Austen Book Club (both 2007), and opposite Liam Neeson as Kim Mills in Taken in 2008. She reprised the role in Taken 2 (2012) and Taken 3 (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4581576</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Donnie Yen</name>
        <birthday>1963-07-27</birthday>
        <age>54</age>
        <biography>Donnie Yen (born 27 July 1963), also known as Yen Ji-dan (甄子丹), is a Chinese actor, martial artist, film director, producer, action choreographer, and multiple-time world wushu tournament champion.[1][2]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3748528</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sienna Miller</name>
        <birthday>1981-12-28</birthday>
        <age>36</age>
        <biography>Sienna Rose Diana Miller[1] (born 28 December 1981)[2] is a British-American actress, model, and fashion designer.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1212428</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ian McShane</name>
        <birthday>1942-09-29</birthday>
        <age>75</age>
        <biography>Ian David McShane[1] (born 29 September 1942) is an English actor and voice artist. He is known for his television roles, particularly the title role in Lovejoy (1986–1994),[2] Al Swearengen in Deadwood (2004–2006), Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides and Winston in John Wick. He is set to portray Mr. Wednesday in the upcoming Starz series American Gods.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4425200</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Colin Firth</name>
        <birthday>1960-09-10</birthday>
        <age>57</age>
        <biography>Colin Andrew Firth, CBE (born 10 September 1960) is an English actor. His films have grossed more than $3 billion from 42 releases worldwide.[1] Firth has received an Academy Award, a Golden Globe Award, two BAFTA Awards, and three Screen Actors Guild Awards, as well as the Volpi Cup. Firth's most notable and acclaimed role to date has been his 2010 portrayal of King George VI in The King's Speech, a performance that earned him an Oscar and multiple worldwide best actor awards.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5028340</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Gal Gadot</name>
        <birthday>1985-04-30</birthday>
        <age>32</age>
        <biography>Gal Gadot-Varsano (/ˈɡɑːl ɡɑːˈdɒt/ GAHL gah-DOT;[2] Hebrew: גל גדות‎‎; born 30 April 1985)[3] is an Israeli actress and model. As an actress, Gadot is known for her role as Gisele Yashar in The Fast and the Furious film series. In 2016, Gadot began playing the role of Wonder Woman in the DC Extended Universe, starting with Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice and continuing as the lead in Wonder Woman (2017).[4][5] She is the first person to portray Wonder Woman in a live-action film. She is a former Israel Defense Forces soldier and served in the Israeli military for two years.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0974015</movie>
            <movie>tt0451279</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jacob Warner</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2119532</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Emma Stone</name>
        <birthday>1988-11-06</birthday>
        <age>29</age>
        <biography>Emily Jean "Emma" Stone (born November 6, 1988) is an American actress. One of the world's highest-paid actresses in 2015, Stone has received such accolades as an Academy Award, a BAFTA Award, a Golden Globe Award and three Screen Actors Guild Awards. She appeared in Forbes Celebrity 100 in 2013, and is often described by the media as one of the most talented actresses of her generation.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3783958</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Hiroyuki Sanada</name>
        <birthday>1960-10-12</birthday>
        <age>57</age>
        <biography>Hiroyuki Sanada, MBE (真田 広之, Sanada Hiroyuki?, born Hiroyuki Shimosawa (下澤 廣之, Shimosawa Hiroyuki?) on October 12, 1960) is a Japanese actor. Sanada is currently a guest star as Takehaya in the apocalyptic drama The Last Ship.[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5442430</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bella Thorne</name>
        <birthday>1997-10-08</birthday>
        <age>20</age>
        <biography>Annabella Avery "Bella" Thorne[2] (born October 8, 1997) is an American actress and singer.[3] She played Ruthy Spivey in the television series My Own Worst Enemy, Tancy Henrickson in the fourth season of Big Love, and CeCe Jones on the Disney Channel series Shake It Up.[4] She also appeared as Hilary/"Larry" in Blended and as Celia in Alexander and the Terrible, Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Day.[5] In 2015, she played Madison in The Duff, Amanda in Perfect High and Hazel in Big Sky.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4042818</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Diego Luna</name>
        <birthday>1979-12-29</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Diego Luna Alexander (Spanish pronunciation: [ˈdjeɣo ˈluna]; born 29 December 1979) is a Mexican actor, producer and director. After starring in telenovelas early in his career, he has appeared in many films, including Y tu mamá también, Dirty Dancing: Havana Nights, Rudo y Cursi and Rogue One. He also provided the Spanish language narration for the National Geographic Channel documentary Great Migrations.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3748528</movie>
            <movie>tt2066055</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ryô Narita</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5311514</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kenneth Welsh</name>
        <birthday>1942-03-30</birthday>
        <age>75</age>
        <biography>Kenneth Welsh, CM (born March 30, 1942) is a Canadian-American film and television actor (sometimes credited as Ken Welsh). He is known to Twin Peaks fans as the multi-faceted villain Windom Earle, and played the father of Katharine Hepburn as portrayed by Cate Blanchett in Martin Scorsese's The Aviator. He lives outside of Toronto.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4255304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Nick Offerman</name>
        <birthday>1970-06-26</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Nicholas "Nick" Offerman (born June 26, 1970) is an American actor, voice actor, producer, screenwriter, author, musician, humorist, stand-up comedian and carpenter widely known for his breakout role as Ron Swanson in the acclaimed NBC sitcom Parks and Recreation, for which he received the Television Critics Association Award for Individual Achievement in Comedy. His first major television role since the end of Parks and Recreation was his role as Karl Weathers in the FX series Fargo, for which he received a Critics' Choice Television Award nomination for Best Supporting Actor in a Movie/Miniseries.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4276820</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Anya Taylor-Joy</name>
        <birthday>1996-04-16</birthday>
        <age>21</age>
        <biography>Anya Taylor-Joy (born 16 April 1996)[1] is an American-born Argentine-British[2] actress.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4972582</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Aneurin Barnard</name>
        <birthday>1987-05-08</birthday>
        <age>30</age>
        <biography>Aneurin Barnard (born 8 May 1987) is a Welsh stage and screen actor. He is best known for his roles as Davey in Hunky Dory, Claude in The Truth About Emanuel, Robert "Bobby" Willis Jr. in Cilla and King Richard III in The White Queen.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5013056</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Joey King</name>
        <birthday>1999-07-30</birthday>
        <age>18</age>
        <biography>Joey Lynn King[1] (born July 30, 1999[2]) is an American actress. She is known for her starring role as Ramona Quimby in Ramona and Beezus, the 2010 adaptation of Beverly Cleary's book series with the same title. She has also appeared in the films Oz the Great and Powerful, The Conjuring and White House Down.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2568862</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Russell Crowe</name>
        <birthday>1964-04-07</birthday>
        <age>53</age>
        <biography>Russell Ira Crowe (born 7 April 1964) is an actor, film producer and musician. Although a New Zealand citizen, he has lived most of his life in Australia.[1] He came to international attention for his role as the Roman General Maximus Decimus Meridius in the 2000 historical epic film Gladiator, directed by Ridley Scott, for which Crowe won an Academy Award for Best Actor, a Broadcast Film Critics Association Award for Best Actor, an Empire Award for Best Actor and a London Film Critics Circle Award for Best Actor and 10 further nominations for best actor.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2345759</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Benedict Cumberbatch</name>
        <birthday>1976-07-19</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Benedict Timothy Carlton Cumberbatch CBE (born 19 July 1976)[2] is an English actor who has performed in film, television, theatre and radio. He is the son of actors Timothy Carlton and Wanda Ventham. Cumberbatch graduated from the University of Manchester and continued his training at the London Academy of Music and Dramatic Art, obtaining a Master of Arts in Classical Acting. He first performed at the Open Air Theatre, Regent's Park in Shakespearean productions and made his West End debut portraying George Tesman in Richard Eyre's revival of Hedda Gabler in 2005. Since then he has starred in the Royal National Theatre productions After the Dance (2010) and Frankenstein (2011). In 2015, he played William Shakespeare's Hamlet at the Barbican Theatre.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1211837</movie>
            <movie>tt3501632</movie>
            <movie>tt2388771</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Cara Delevingne</name>
        <birthday>1992-08-12</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Cara Jocelyn Delevingne (/ˈkɑːrə ˌdɛləˈviːn/ KAH-rə DEL-ə-VEEN;[6][7] born 12 August 1992)[8][9] is an English fashion model and actress.[10][11][12] She signed with Storm Model Management after leaving school in 2009.[13] Delevingne won the "Model of the Year" award at the British Fashion Awards in 2012 and 2014 and has appeared in shows for houses including Burberry, Mulberry, Dolce &amp; Gabbana, and Jason Wu.[14] She started her acting career with a minor role in the 2012 film adaptation of Anna Karenina. Her first major roles were as Margo Roth Spiegelman in the romantic mystery film Paper Towns (2015), Kath Talent in London Fields, and the Enchantress in the comic book film Suicide Squad (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2239822</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Taron Egerton</name>
        <birthday>1989-11-10</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Taron David Egerton[1] (born 10 November 1989) is a Welsh actor.[2][3] He is known for his roles in the British television series The Smoke and the 2014 action comedy film Kingsman: The Secret Service.[4][5] He played Edward Brittain in the 2014 drama film Testament of Youth, appeared in the 2015 crime thriller film Legend, and starred as Eddie "The Eagle" Edwards in the 2016 biographical film Eddie the Eagle. He also voiced Johnny in the 2016 animated musical film Sing. His upcoming films include Billionaire Boys Club (2017) and Kingsman: The Golden Circle (2017).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4649466</movie>
            <movie>tt4532826</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Patrick Wilson</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1477834</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dakota Johnson</name>
        <birthday>1989-10-04</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Dakota Mayi Johnson (born October 4, 1989) is an American actress and model. She is the daughter of actors Melanie Griffith and Don Johnson. She had her screen debut alongside her mother in the comedy-drama Crazy in Alabama (1999) and was named Miss Golden Globe in 2006. Following high school graduation, she returned to acting with roles in The Social Network (2010), Beastly (2011), 21 Jump Street (2012), Need for Speed (2014) and the short-lived comedy Ben and Kate (2012–2013).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4465564</movie>
            <movie>tt4477536</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ali Larter</name>
        <birthday>1976-02-28</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Alison Elizabeth "Ali" Larter (born February 28, 1976[1][2]) is an American actress. She portrayed fictional model Allegra Coleman in a 1996 Esquire magazine hoax and took on guest roles on several television shows in the 1990s. She made her film debut in Varsity Blues (1999), which was followed by the horror films House on Haunted Hill (1999), Final Destination (2000) and Final Destination 2 (2003).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2592614</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jennifer Aniston</name>
        <birthday>1969-02-11</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Jennifer Joanna Aniston (born February 11, 1969)[1] is an American actress, producer, and businesswoman.[2] She is the daughter of Greek-born actor John Aniston and American actress Nancy Dow. Aniston gained worldwide recognition for portraying Rachel Green on the popular television sitcom Friends (1994–2004), a role which earned her a Primetime Emmy Award, a Golden Globe Award, and a Screen Actors Guild Award. The character was widely popular during the airing of the series and was later recognized as one of the 100 greatest female characters in United States television.[3][4]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1711525</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Steve Buscemi</name>
        <birthday>1957-12-13</birthday>
        <age>60</age>
        <biography>Steven Vincent "Steve" Buscemi (/buːˈsɛmi/[1] born December 13, 1957) is an American actor and film director. Buscemi has starred and supported in successful Hollywood and indie films, including Parting Glances, New York Stories, Mystery Train, Reservoir Dogs, Desperado, Con Air, Armageddon, The Grey Zone, Ghost World, Big Fish, and The Sopranos. He is also known for his appearances in many films by the Coen brothers: Miller's Crossing, Barton Fink, The Hudsucker Proxy, Fargo, and The Big Lebowski. Buscemi provides the voice of Randall Boggs in the Monsters, Inc. franchise.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3874544</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tyler Hoechlin</name>
        <birthday>1987-09-11</birthday>
        <age>30</age>
        <biography>Tyler Lee Hoechlin (/ˈhɛklɪn/; September 11, 1987) is an American actor. He got his big break starring as Michael Sullivan, Jr. in the film Road to Perdition (2002). For television he is known for playing the role of Martin Brewer on 7th Heaven and the role of Derek Hale on the MTV series Teen Wolf. In 2016, Hoechlin was cast as Superman on the CW show Supergirl.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4477536</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sam Riley</name>
        <birthday>1980-01-08</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Samuel Peter W. "Sam" Riley[1] (born 8 January 1980) is an English actor and singer.[2] He is best known for his performance in the 2007 biographical film Control, about the life of Ian Curtis, and as Diaval in the 2014 film Maleficent.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4158096</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael B. Jordan</name>
        <birthday>1987-02-09</birthday>
        <age>30</age>
        <biography>Michael Bakari Jordan (born February 9, 1987) is an American actor. His television roles include East Dillon High School quarterback Vince Howard in Friday Night Lights, teenage drug-dealer Wallace in The Wire, Reggie Montgomery in All My Children, and Alex in Parenthood.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1825683</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Eric Bell Jr.</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3874544</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Matt Damon</name>
        <birthday>1970-10-08</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Matthew Paige Damon (/ˈdeɪmən/; born October 8, 1970)[2] is an American actor, film producer, and screenwriter. He is ranked among Forbes magazine's most bankable stars[3] and is one of the highest-grossing actors of all time.[4][nb 1] Damon has received various accolades, including an Academy Award from five nominations, two Golden Globe Awards from eight nominations, and has been nominated for two British Academy Film Awards and six Emmy Awards.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2034800</movie>
            <movie>tt5164214</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ben Mendelsohn</name>
        <birthday>1969-04-03</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Paul Benjamin "Ben" Mendelsohn (born 3 April 1969) is an Australian actor, who first rose to prominence in Australia for his role in The Year My Voice Broke (1987) and internationally for his role in the crime drama Animal Kingdom (2010).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4532826</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tangie Ambrose</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4501244</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Oscar Isaac</name>
        <birthday>1979-03-09</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Oscar Isaac (born Óscar Isaac Hernández Estrada; March 9, 1979)[4][5][6] is a Guatemalan-American actor and musician. He is known for his lead film roles in the comedy-drama Inside Llewyn Davis (2013), for which he received a Golden Globe Award nomination, the crime drama A Most Violent Year (2014) and the science fiction thriller Ex Machina (2015), in which he played Nathan Hamlet Bateman. In 2006, he portrayed Saint Joseph, husband of Mary, in The Nativity Story. He also portrayed José Ramos-Horta, former president of East Timor, in the Australian film Balibo for which he won the AACTA Award for Best Actor in a Supporting Role. He has portrayed characters of many different nationalities and ethnicities, such as mixed European, Egyptian, Polish, English, French, Mexican, East Timorese, Welsh, Indonesian, Greek, Cuban, Israeli, and Armenian.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4776998</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jason Momoa</name>
        <birthday>1979-08-01</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Joseph Jason Namakaeha Momoa (born August 1, 1979) is an American actor, model, director, writer, and producer. He is known for his television roles as Ronon Dex on the military science fiction television series Stargate Atlantis (2004–2009) and as Khal Drogo in the HBO fantasy television series Game of Thrones (2011–2012).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0974015</movie>
            <movie>tt1477834</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jude Law</name>
        <birthday>1972-12-29</birthday>
        <age>45</age>
        <biography>David Jude Heyworth Law (born 29 December 1972) is an English actor. He has received nominations for two Academy Awards, two Screen Actors Guild Awards, three Golden Globe Awards and two British Academy Awards, winning one. In 2007, he received an Honorary César and was named a Chevalier of the Order of Arts and Letters by the French government.[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1972591</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tom Cullen</name>
        <birthday>1985-07-17</birthday>
        <age>32</age>
        <biography>Tom Cullen (born 17 July 1985) is a Welsh actor, writer and director. He is best known for his role in the award-winning independent film Weekend (2011) and as Viscount Gillingham in the television series Downton Abbey.[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3707104</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Cedric the Entertainer</name>
        <birthday>1964-04-24</birthday>
        <age>53</age>
        <biography>Cedric Antonio Kyles (born April 24, 1964), better known by his stage name, Cedric the Entertainer, is an American actor, comedian, director, and game show host. He was originally the host on It's Showtime at the Apollo. He also hosted BET's ComicView during the 1993-1994 season and Def Comedy Jam in 1995. He is best known for co-starring with Steve Harvey on The WB sitcom The Steve Harvey Show and starring as Eddie in Barbershop. He hosted the twelfth season of daytime version of Who Wants to Be a Millionaire in the 2013-2014 television season. He also starred in the TV Land original series The Soul Man, which aired its fifth and final season in 2016.[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4501244</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Mark Wahlberg</name>
        <birthday>1971-06-05</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Mark Robert Michael Wahlberg (born June 5, 1971)[2] is an American actor, producer, businessman, former model, and rapper. Mark was known as Marky Mark in his early career as frontman for the group Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch, releasing the albums Music for the People and You Gotta Believe. Wahlberg later transitioned to acting, appearing in films such as the drama Boogie Nights and the satirical war comedy-drama Three Kings during the 1990s. In the 2000s, he starred in the biographical disaster drama The Perfect Storm, the science fiction film Planet of the Apes, the heist film The Italian Job, and the Martin Scorsese-directed neo-noir crime drama The Departed, for which he received an Academy Award nomination for Best Supporting Actor. In the 2010s, he starred in the action comedy The Other Guys alongside Will Ferrell, the biographical sports drama The Fighter (for which he earned an Academy Award nomination as a producer for Best Picture), the comedy Ted, the war film Lone Survivor, the crime comedy Pain &amp; Gain, the science fiction action film Transformers: Age of Extinction, the disaster film Deepwater Horizon, and the thriller Patriots Day.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4572514</movie>
            <movie>tt3371366</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Casey Affleck</name>
        <birthday>1975-08-12</birthday>
        <age>42</age>
        <biography>Caleb Casey McGuire Affleck-Boldt[1] (born August 12, 1975) is an American actor and director. He began his career as a child actor, appearing in the PBS television movie Lemon Sky (1988) and the ABC miniseries The Kennedys of Massachusetts (1990). He later appeared in three Gus Van Sant films – To Die For (1995), Good Will Hunting (1997), and Gerry (2002) – and in Steven Soderbergh's comedy heist trilogy Ocean's Eleven (2001), Ocean's Twelve (2004) and Ocean's Thirteen (2007). His first leading role was in Steve Buscemi's independent comedy-drama Lonesome Jim (2006).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4034228</movie>
            <movie>tt2837574</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Pamela Anderson</name>
        <birthday>1967-07-01 1967-07-01</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Pamela Denise Anderson (born July 1, 1967)[1][2][3] is a Canadian American actress and model known for her roles on the television series Home Improvement, Baywatch and V.I.P.. She was Playmate of the Month for Playboy magazine in February 1990.[4] Anderson was inducted into Canada's Walk of Fame in 2006.[5]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1469304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tim Blake Nelson</name>
        <birthday>1964-05-11</birthday>
        <age>53</age>
        <biography>Timothy Blake Nelson (born May 11, 1964) is an American actor, writer and director. Nelson has had a wide career becoming a recognizable character actor of sorts. His most famous roles include Delmar O'Donnell in O Brother, Where Art Thou? (2000), Dr. Pendanski in Holes (2003), Daniel "Danny" Dalton Jr. in Syriana (2005), and Dr. Samuel Sterns in The Incredible Hulk (2008).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4680182</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Karan Soni</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1431045</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Demetrius Shipp Jr.</name>
        <birthday>1988-11-20</birthday>
        <age>29</age>
        <biography>Demetrius Shipp Jr. (born November 20, 1988) is an American actor who will portray the late Tupac Shakur in the upcoming 2017 biopic All Eyez on Me.[1][2] He will star alongside Jamal Woolard, who also played The Notorious B.I.G. in the 2009 film Notorious.[3]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1666185</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tian Jing</name>
        <birthday>1988-07-21</birthday>
        <age>29</age>
        <biography>Jing Tian (born July 21, 1988, in Xi'an, Shaanxi, China) is a Chinese actress. She graduated from the Beijing Dance Academy and Beijing Film Academy. She is known for her roles in The Warring States, Special ID, and Police Story 2013. She is part of the cast for three Legendary Pictures films, 2016's The Great Wall, 2017's Kong: Skull Island, and the upcoming Pacific Rim: Uprising.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2034800</movie>
            <movie>tt2557478</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Thomas Brodie-Sangster</name>
        <birthday>1990-05-16</birthday>
        <age>27</age>
        <biography>Thomas Brodie-Sangster (born 16 May 1990), also credited as Thomas Sangster, is an English actor and musician, known for his roles as Jojen Reed in Game of Thrones, his voice as Ferb Fletcher in Phineas and Ferb, as John Tracy in the ITV series Thunderbirds Are Go, as well as his roles as Sam in Richard Curtis's Love Actually and Newt in the Maze Runner film series. Sangster also grew in popularity for starring in critically acclaimed cult films such as Death of a Superhero, Bright Star and as Paul McCartney in Nowhere Boy. He also had a cameo in the 2015 film Star Wars: The Force Awakens.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4500922</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Haley Bennett</name>
        <birthday>1988-01-07</birthday>
        <age>29</age>
        <biography>Haley Loraine Keeling (born January 7, 1988),[1] known professionally as Haley Bennett, is an American actress and singer. She made her film debut as pop star Cora Corman in the romantic comedy Music and Lyrics (2007). She has since appeared in the films The Haunting of Molly Hartley (2008), College (2008), The Hole (2009), Kaboom (2010), The Equalizer (2014), Kristy (2014), Hardcore Henry (2015), The Magnificent Seven (2016), and The Girl on the Train (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3631112</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dakota Fanning</name>
        <birthday>1994-02-23</birthday>
        <age>23</age>
        <biography>Hannah Dakota Fanning (born February 23, 1994)[1] is an American actress and model. At age seven, her performance in the 2001 film I Am Sam earned her a nomination for a Screen Actors Guild Award at age eight in 2002, making her the youngest nominee in history.[2] As a child actress, she went on to appear in high-profile films such as Man on Fire (2004), War of the Worlds (2005) and Charlotte's Web (2006).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1895315</movie>
            <movie>tt5164214</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Daniel Zovatto</name>
        <birthday>1991-06-28</birthday>
        <age>26</age>
        <biography>Daniel Zovatto (born June 28, 1991) is a Costa Rican film and television actor. Since 2012, he has starred in films of the horror genre, Beneath (2013), It Follows (2014), and Don't Breathe (2016), as well as the romantic comedy Laggies (2014). Zovatto made his television debut in 2014, guest starring in an episode of Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. He has since held recurring roles as Gideon LeMarchal in Revenge (2014), and Jack in Fear the Walking Dead (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4160708</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Simon Pegg</name>
        <birthday>1970-02-14</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Simon John Pegg (né Beckingham;[1][2] born 14 February 1970)[3] is an English actor, comedian, screenwriter, and producer. He co-wrote and starred in the Three Flavours Cornetto trilogy of films: Shaun of the Dead (2004), Hot Fuzz (2007), and The World's End (2013). He and Nick Frost wrote and starred in the sci-fi film Paul (2011). Pegg portrayed Benji Dunn in the Mission: Impossible film series (2006-present) and Montgomery Scott in Star Trek (2009), Star Trek Into Darkness (2013), and Star Trek Beyond (2016), co-writing the latter.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1677720</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Thomas Lennon</name>
        <birthday>1970-08-09</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Thomas Patrick Lennon (born August 9, 1970) is an American actor, comedian, screenwriter, producer and director best known as a cast member on MTV's The State, for his role as Lieutenant Jim Dangle on the Comedy Central series Reno 911! and as Felix Unger on the CBS series The Odd Couple. He is the writing partner of Robert Ben Garant.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3095734</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Abbey Lee</name>
        <birthday>1987-06-12</birthday>
        <age>30</age>
        <biography>Abbey Lee Kershaw (born 12 June 1987), known professionally as Abbey Lee,[2] is an Australian fashion model, actress and musician.[3][4] Following several years of success leading up to the 2011 fashion seasons, V magazine dubbed Kershaw a supermodel.[5] Models.com has listed her as an "Industry Icon".[6]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1648190</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Chris Pine</name>
        <birthday>1980-08-26</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Christopher Whitelaw "Chris" Pine[1] (born August 26, 1980)[2] is an American actor. He is known for his role as James T. Kirk in Star Trek (2009), Star Trek Into Darkness (2013), and Star Trek Beyond (2016). He also appeared in the films The Princess Diaries 2: Royal Engagement (2004), Just My Luck (2006), Smokin' Aces (2007), Bottle Shock (2008), Unstoppable (2010), This Means War (2012), Rise of the Guardians (2012), Horrible Bosses 2 (2014), Jack Ryan: Shadow Recruit (2014), Into the Woods (2014), Z for Zachariah (2015), The Finest Hours (2016), and Hell or High Water (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0451279</movie>
            <movie>tt1620680</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bel Powley</name>
        <birthday>1992-03-07</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Isobel Dorothy "Bel" Powley (born 7 March 1992) is an English actress best known for playing Daisy Miller in the CBBC television series M.I. High. Powley plays the protagonist in the 2015 film The Diary of a Teenage Girl, which premiered at the 2015 Sundance Film Festival.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4537896</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Gugu Mbatha-Raw</name>
        <birthday>1983-04-21</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Gugulethu Sophia Mbatha (born 21 April[1] 1983),[2][3] known as Gugu Mbatha-Raw (pronounced /ˈɡuːɡuː mmˈbɑːtə rɔː/),[4] is a British stage and film actress.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1620680</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Alec Baldwin</name>
        <birthday>1958-04-03</birthday>
        <age>59</age>
        <biography>Alexander Rae "Alec" Baldwin III (born April 3, 1958) is an American actor, writer, producer, and comedian.[1] A member of the Baldwin family, he is the oldest of the four Baldwin brothers, all actors. Baldwin first gained recognition appearing on seasons 6 and 7 of the CBS television drama Knots Landing, in the role of Joshua Rush. He has since played both leading and supporting roles in films such as the horror comedy fantasy film Beetlejuice (1988), as Jack Ryan in the action thriller The Hunt for Red October (1990), the romantic comedy The Marrying Man (1991), the superhero film The Shadow (1994), and two films directed by Martin Scorsese: the Howard Hughes biopic The Aviator (2004) and the neo-noir crime drama The Departed (2006). His performance in the 2003 romantic drama The Cooler garnered him a nomination for the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3874544</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ike Barinholtz</name>
        <birthday>1977-02-18</birthday>
        <age>40</age>
        <biography>Isaac "Ike" Barinholtz (born February 18, 1977) is an American actor, comedian, voice actor and screenwriter. He was a cast member on MADtv from 2002 to 2007, Eastbound &amp; Down (2012) and currently has a regular role on The Mindy Project. In his film work, he is best known for his acting roles in Neighbors (2014) and its sequel, Neighbors 2: Sorority Rising (2016), Sisters (2015), and Suicide Squad (2016), as well for as co-writing the screenplay for the 2016 comedy film Central Intelligence.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1386697</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Robert De Niro</name>
        <birthday>1943-08-17</birthday>
        <age>74</age>
        <biography>Robert Anthony De Niro (/dəˈnɪroʊ/; born August 17, 1943) is an American actor, producer and director who has both Italian and American citizenship.[1][2] He was cast as the young Vito Corleone in the 1974 film The Godfather Part II, for which he won the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor. His longtime collaboration with director Martin Scorsese earned him the Academy Award for Best Actor for his portrayal of Jake La Motta in the 1980 film Raging Bull. He received the AFI Life Achievement Award in 2003, the Golden Globe Cecil B. DeMille Award in 2010, and the Presidential Medal of Freedom from President Barack Obama in 2016.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1302006</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Priyanka Bose</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3741834</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ted Levine</name>
        <birthday>1957-05-29</birthday>
        <age>60</age>
        <biography>Frank Theodore "Ted" Levine (born May 29, 1957) is an American actor. He is known for his roles as Buffalo Bill in The Silence of the Lambs and as Captain Leland Stottlemeyer in the television series Monk.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4881806</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Hugh Jackman</name>
        <birthday>1968-10-12</birthday>
        <age>49</age>
        <biography>Hugh Michael Jackman (born 12 October 1968)[1] is an Australian actor, singer, and producer. Jackman has won international recognition for his roles in a variety of film genres. He is known for his long-running role as Wolverine in the X-Men film series, as well as for his lead roles in films such as the romantic-comedy fantasy Kate &amp; Leopold (2001), the action-horror film Van Helsing (2004), the magic-themed drama The Prestige (2006), the epic fantasy drama The Fountain (2006), the epic historical romantic drama Australia (2008), the film version of Les Misérables (2012), and the thriller Prisoners (2013). His work in Les Misérables earned him his first Academy Award nomination for Best Actor and his first Golden Globe Award for Best Actor – Motion Picture Musical or Comedy in 2013.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3315342</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>James McAvoy</name>
        <birthday>1979-04-21</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>James McAvoy (/ˈmækəvɔɪ/; born 21 April 1979)[2] is a Scottish actor. He made his acting début as a teen in 1995's The Near Room and continued to make mostly television appearances until 2003, when his feature film career began and he continued to work in both areas from then on. His notable television work includes the drama show State of Play, the adult comedy-drama Shameless, and the science fiction show Frank Herbert's Children of Dune.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4972582</movie>
            <movie>tt3385516</movie>
            <movie>tt2406566</movie>
            <movie>tt2296777</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bill Paxton</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4287320</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Cate Blanchett</name>
        <birthday>1969-05-14</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Catherine Elise "Cate" Blanchett[1] (/ˈblæntʃət/;[2] born 14 May 1969) is an Australian actress and theatre director. She has received international acclaim and many accolades, including six AACTA Awards, two Academy Awards, three Screen Actors Guild Awards, three Golden Globe Awards, and three BAFTA Awards. Blanchett came to international attention for her role as Elizabeth I of England in Shekhar Kapur's 1998 film Elizabeth, for which she won the BAFTA Award for Best Actress, the Golden Globe Award, and earned her first Academy Award for Best Actress nomination. Her portrayal of Katharine Hepburn in Martin Scorsese's 2004 film The Aviator brought her critical acclaim and many accolades, including the Academy Award for Best Actress in a Supporting Role, making her the only actor to win an Oscar for portraying another Oscar-winning actor. In 2013, she starred as Jasmine Francis in Woody Allen's Blue Jasmine, for which she won numerous accolades including the Academy Award for Best Actress.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5164214</movie>
            <movie>tt2388771</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kaya Scodelario</name>
        <birthday>1992-03-13</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Kaya Scodelario-Davis[1] (born Kaya Rose Humphrey; March 13, 1992) is an English actress of Italian-Brazilian descent. She made her acting debut as Effy Stonem on the E4 teen drama Skins (2007-2010), for which she received recognition and critical praise, garnering two Golden Nymph Award nominations for Outstanding Actress in a Drama Series and two TV Quick Award nominations for Best Actress. Following her film debut in the science-fiction film Moon (2009) and a role in the fantasy adventure film Clash of the Titans (2010), Scodelario was nominated for the Glamour Award for PANDORA Breakthrough for her portrayal of Catherine Earnshaw in the 2011 film adaptation of Emily Brontë's novel Wuthering Heights.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1790809</movie>
            <movie>tt4500922</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Amiée Conn</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3783958</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Arielle Kebbel</name>
        <birthday>1985-02-19</birthday>
        <age>32</age>
        <biography>Arielle Caroline Kebbel (born February 19, 1985) is an American model and actress. She is known for her television roles on The Vampire Diaries, True Blood, Life Unexpected, 90210, Gilmore Girls, UnREAL, and Ballers.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4477536</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Javier Bardem</name>
        <birthday>1969-03-01</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Javier Ángel Encinas Bardem (Spanish pronunciation: [xaˈβjer βarˈðen];[2][3] born 1 March 1969) is a Spanish actor. Bardem won the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for his role as the psychopathic assassin Anton Chigurh in the 2007 Coen brothers film No Country for Old Men. He has also received critical acclaim for roles in films such as Jamón, jamón, Carne trémula, Boca a boca, Los Lunes al sol, Mar adentro, and Skyfall, for which he received both a BAFTA and a SAG nomination for Best Supporting Actor.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1790809</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Paul Anderson</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4532826</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Connie Nielsen</name>
        <birthday>1965-07-03</birthday>
        <age>52</age>
        <biography>Connie Inge-Lise Nielsen (born 3 July 1965) is a Danish actress whose first major role in an English language film was a supporting role in The Devil's Advocate (1997); Nielsen later gained international attention for her role in Ridley Scott's Gladiator (2000). Her films include Mission to Mars (2000), One Hour Photo (2002), Basic (2003), The Hunted (2003), The Ice Harvest (2005) and Nymphomaniac (2014). She starred as Meredith Kane on the Starz TV series Boss (2011–2012) and was a lead character in the second season of The Following. She is set to play Queen Hippolyta in the upcoming 2017 film Wonder Woman.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0451279</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Samuel L. Jackson</name>
        <birthday>1948-12-21</birthday>
        <age>69</age>
        <biography>Samuel Leroy Jackson (born December 21, 1948) is an American actor and film producer. He achieved prominence and critical acclaim in the early 1990s with films such as Jungle Fever (1991), Patriot Games (1992), Amos &amp; Andrew (1993), True Romance (1993), Jurassic Park (1993) and his collaborations with director Quentin Tarantino including Pulp Fiction (1994), Jackie Brown (1997), Django Unchained (2012), and The Hateful Eight (2015). He is a highly prolific actor, having appeared in over 100 films, including Die Hard with a Vengeance (1995), Unbreakable (2000), Shaft (2000), The 51st State (2001), Black Snake Moan (2006), Snakes on a Plane (2006), and the Star Wars prequel trilogy (1999–2005), as well as the Marvel Cinematic Universe.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3731562</movie>
            <movie>tt3606756</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Nicholas Hoult</name>
        <birthday>1989-12-07</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Nicholas Caradoc Hoult[1] (born 7 December 1989)[2][3][4] is an English actor. Hoult made his professional acting debut at the age of seven in the 1996 film Intimate Relations. He received recognition after landing the role of Marcus Brewer in About a Boy, for which he was nominated for the Critics' Choice Movie Award for Best Young Performer. He received further acclaim for his performance as Tony Stonem in the E4 teen drama Skins.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3385516</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Scoot McNairy</name>
        <birthday>1977-11-11</birthday>
        <age>40</age>
        <biography>John Marcus "Scoot" McNairy[1] (born November 11, 1977)[1] is an American actor and producer known for his roles in films such as Monsters, Argo, Killing Them Softly, 12 Years a Slave, Frank, Gone Girl and Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice.[2] He currently stars in the AMC period drama Halt and Catch Fire.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2072233</movie>
            <movie>tt4581576</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jason Sudeikis</name>
        <birthday>1975-09-18</birthday>
        <age>42</age>
        <biography>Daniel Jason Sudeikis (/sᵿˈdeɪkɪs/ su-DAY-kiss; born September 18, 1975),[1] better known as Jason Sudeikis, is an American comedian, actor, screenwriter and producer. He began his career in improv comedy. In 2003, he was hired as a sketch writer for Saturday Night Live and was a cast member from 2005 to 2013. He has appeared on television in 30 Rock, The Cleveland Show, Eastbound &amp; Down, The Last Man on Earth, Son of Zorn, and other shows. He is also known for his roles in the films Hall Pass (2011), Horrible Bosses (2011), Epic (2013), We're the Millers (2013), Horrible Bosses 2 (2014), Sleeping with Other People (2015), the voice of Red in The Angry Birds Movie (2016), and a dramatic role in Race (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4680182</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Keaton</name>
        <birthday>1951-09-05</birthday>
        <age>66</age>
        <biography>Michael John Douglas (born September 5, 1951),[1] known professionally as Michael Keaton, is an American actor, producer, and director. Keaton first rose to fame for his comedic film roles in Night Shift (1982), Mr. Mom (1983), Johnny Dangerously (1984) and Beetlejuice (1988), and he earned further acclaim for his dramatic portrayal of the title character in Tim Burton's Batman (1989) and Batman Returns (1992).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4276820</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Robert Pattinson</name>
        <birthday>1986-05-13</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Robert Douglas Thomas Pattinson[1][2] (born 13 May 1986)[3][4] is an English actor, producer, model, and musician.[5]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1212428</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rabah Nait Oufella</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4954522</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Janelle Monáe</name>
        <birthday>1985-12-01</birthday>
        <age>32</age>
        <biography>Janelle Monáe Robinson (born December 1, 1985),[9] known professionally as Janelle Monáe (/dʒəˈnɛl moʊˈneɪ/),[10] is an American singer, songwriter, actress, and model signed to her own imprint, Wondaland Arts Society, and Atlantic Records. After making a mark with her first unofficial studio album, The Audition, she publicly debuted with a conceptual EP titled Metropolis: Suite I (The Chase), which peaked at number 115 on the Billboard 200 in the United States.[11]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4846340</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tobias Menzies</name>
        <birthday>1974-03-07</birthday>
        <age>43</age>
        <biography>Tobias Menzies (born 7 March 1974) is an English stage, television and film actor. While working in theatre, he starred in television shows such as Rome (2005–2007) where he played Brutus and Game of Thrones (2013–present) where he plays Edmure Tully. He is also known for his dual role as Frank Randall and Jonathan "Black Jack" Randall in Outlander (2014–present), for which he received a Golden Globe Award nomination.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3717252</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Chris Evans</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3498820</movie>
            <movie>tt4481414</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dafne Keen</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3315342</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Sheen</name>
        <birthday>1969-02-05</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Michael Christopher Sheen, OBE (born 5 February 1969)[1][2] is a Welsh actor and political activist. After training at London's Royal Academy of Dramatic Art (RADA), he worked mainly in theatre throughout the 1990s and made notable stage appearances in Romeo and Juliet (1992), Don't Fool With Love (1993), Peer Gynt (1994), The Seagull (1995), The Homecoming (1997), and Henry V (1997). His performances in Amadeus at the Old Vic and Look Back in Anger at the National Theatre were nominated for Olivier Awards in 1998 and 1999, respectively. In 2003, he was nominated for a third Olivier Award for his performance in Caligula at the Donmar Warehouse.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1355644</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kathleen Munroe</name>
        <birthday>1982-04-09</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Kathleen Munroe (born 9 April 1982) is a Canadian actress.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4255304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Karen Gillan</name>
        <birthday>1987-11-28</birthday>
        <age>30</age>
        <biography>Karen Sheila Gillan (born 28 November 1987) is a Scottish actress and director. She is known for the role of Amelia Pond, companion to the Eleventh Doctor, in the BBC science fiction series Doctor Who (2010–13). In film, she has starred as Jane Lockhart in Not Another Happy Ending (2013), Kaylie Russell in the horror film Oculus (2013), and Nebula in the Marvel film Guardians of the Galaxy (2014) and its sequel Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2 (2017). She took part in the upcoming films Jumanji (2017), The Circle (2017), Avengers: Infinity War (2018) and its untitled sequel (2019). In 2017, she directed her first feature film Tupperware Party.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3896198</movie>
            <movie>tt4287320</movie>
            <movie>tt2283362</movie>
            <movie>tt4154756</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Mckenna Grace</name>
        <birthday>2006-06-25</birthday>
        <age>11</age>
        <biography>Mckenna Grace (born June 25, 2006[1]) is an American child actress known for playing the role of Jasmine Bernstein in the series Crash &amp; Bernstein and Faith Newman in The Young and the Restless. As of 2016[update], she plays Penny Kirkman in the ABC television series Designated Survivor. Grace is also in the TV series Once Upon a Time as young Emma. She is set to appear in the upcoming film, How to Be a Latin Lover as Arden.[2]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4481414</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rosario Dawson</name>
        <birthday>1979-05-09</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Rosario Isabel Dawson[2] (born May 9, 1979) is an American actress, producer, and comic book writer. She made her film debut in the 1995 teen drama Kids. Her subsequent film roles include He Got Game (1998), Men in Black II (2002), 25th Hour (2002), The Rundown (2003), Alexander (2004), Rent (2005), Sin City (2005), Clerks II (2006), Death Proof (2007), Eagle Eye (2008), Seven Pounds (2008), Percy Jackson &amp; the Olympians: The Lightning Thief (2010), Unstoppable (2010), César Chávez (2013), Trance (2013), and Top Five (2014).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3462710</movie>
            <movie>tt4116284</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jamie Foxx</name>
        <birthday>1967-12-13</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Eric Marlon Bishop (born December 13, 1967),[1] known professionally by his stage name Jamie Foxx, is an American actor, singer, songwriter, record producer and comedian. He won an Academy Award for Best Actor, BAFTA Award for Best Actor in a Leading Role, and Golden Globe Award for Best Actor in a Musical or Comedy, for his portrayal of Ray Charles in the 2004 biographical film Ray. The same year, he was nominated for the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for his role in the crime film Collateral.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2072233</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Walton Goggins</name>
        <birthday>1971-11-10</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Walton Sanders Goggins Jr. (born November 10, 1971)[1] is an American actor. On television, he played Shane Vendrell in The Shield and Boyd Crowder in Justified. He has also appeared in films, such as That Evening Sun, The Apostle, Chrystal, Miracle at St. Anna, Predators, Lincoln, Django Unchained, Machete Kills, American Ultra and The Hateful Eight. He co-produced and starred in the 2001 short film The Accountant, which won an Academy Award for Best Live Action Short Film.[2]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1365519</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Daniel Brühl</name>
        <birthday>1978-06-16</birthday>
        <age>39</age>
        <biography>Daniel César Martín Brühl González (German pronun­cia­tion: [ˈbʁyːl ˈgɔnt͡s.aˌləs] ( listen); born 16 June 1978) is a German actor. He began his work at a young age in a German soap opera called Forbidden Love in 1995. In 2003, his starring role in the German film Good Bye, Lenin! received wider recognition and critical acclaim which garnered him the European Film Award for Best Actor and the German Film Award for Best Actor. Brühl has worked in both European and American productions in several different languages.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1730768</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Milo Gibson</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2119532</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tom Hardy</name>
        <birthday>1977-09-15</birthday>
        <age>40</age>
        <biography>Edward Thomas "Tom" Hardy[1] (born 15 September 1977)[2] is an English actor and producer. His motion picture debut was in Ridley Scott's 2001 action film Black Hawk Down. Hardy's other notable films include the science fiction film Star Trek: Nemesis (2002), the crime film RocknRolla (2008), biographical psychological drama Bronson (2008), sports drama Warrior (2011), Cold War espionage film Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy (2011), crime drama Lawless (2012), drama Locke (2013), mobster film The Drop (2014), and the biographical western thriller The Revenant (2015), for which he received an Academy Award nomination for Best Supporting Actor. He portrayed "Mad" Max Rockatansky in the post-apocalyptic film Mad Max: Fury Road (2015), and both of the Kray twins in the crime thriller Legend (2015). He has appeared in three Christopher Nolan films: the science fiction thriller Inception (2010), portrayed Bane in the superhero film The Dark Knight Rises (2012), and the action-thriller Dunkirk (2017) based on the British evacuation in World War II.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2527336</movie>
            <movie>tt5013056</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jon Bernthal</name>
        <birthday>1976-09-20</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Jonathan Edward "Jon" Bernthal[1] (born September 20, 1976)[2] is an American actor best known for his television role as Shane Walsh on the AMC series The Walking Dead and film roles in The Wolf of Wall Street (2013), Fury (2014), Sicario (2015), and The Accountant (2016). He portrayed Joe Teague in Mob City and Frank Castle (a.k.a. The Punisher) in the Netflix series Daredevil, and is set to reprise the latter role in the Netflix series The Punisher.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2140479</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Johan Heldenbergh</name>
        <birthday>1967-02-09</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Johan Heldenbergh (born 9 February 1967) is a Belgian actor, playwright, screenwriter, theatre director and film director. He gained international fame by starring in films such as A Day in a Life (2007), Moscow, Belgium (2008), The Misfortunates (2009) and The Broken Circle Breakdown (2012).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1730768</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ben Kingsley</name>
        <birthday>1943-12-31</birthday>
        <age>74</age>
        <biography>Sir Ben Kingsley (born Krishna Bhanji; 31 December 1943)[2] is an English actor with a career spanning over 40 years. He has won an Oscar, Grammy, BAFTA, two Golden Globes, and a Screen Actors Guild Award. He is known for his starring role as Mohandas Gandhi in the 1982 film Gandhi, for which he won the Academy Award for Best Actor. He is also known for his performances in the films Schindler's List (1993), Twelfth Night (1996), Sexy Beast (2000), Lucky Number Slevin (2006), Shutter Island (2010), Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time (2010), Hugo (2011), and Iron Man 3 (2013).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6533240</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tadanobu Asano</name>
        <birthday>1973-11-27</birthday>
        <age>44</age>
        <biography>Tadanobu Satō (佐藤 忠信, Satō Tadanobu?, born November 27, 1973), better known by his stage name Tadanobu Asano (浅野 忠信, Asano Tadanobu?), is a Japanese actor and musician.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0490215</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sofia Boutella</name>
        <birthday>1982-04-03</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Sofia Boutella (born April 3, 1982) is an Algerian dancer, model, and actress. She is known mainly for her hip-hop and street dance, and for appearing in Nike Women's advertising campaigns. Boutella has starred as Eva in StreetDance 2 (2012), Ara in Monsters: Dark Continent (2014), Gazelle in Kingsman: The Secret Service (2015), and an alien warrior named Jaylah in Star Trek Beyond (2016). She will be playing the title role in Universal's upcoming film The Mummy (2017).[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2345759</movie>
            <movie>tt2406566</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Taraji P. Henson</name>
        <birthday>1970-09-11</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Taraji Penda Henson[1][2] (/təˈrɑːdʒi/ tə-RAH-jee; born September 11, 1970) is an American actress and author. She studied acting at Howard University and began her Hollywood career in guest-roles on several television shows before making her breakthrough in Baby Boy (2001). She received praise for playing a prostitute in Hustle &amp; Flow (2005) and a single mother in David Fincher's The Curious Case of Benjamin Button (2008); for the latter, she received an Academy Award, SAG Award and Critics Choice Award nominations for Best Supporting Actress, for the former; she received a Screen Actors Guild Award for Outstanding Performance by a Cast in a Motion Picture nomination. In 2010, she appeared in the comedy Date Night and co-starred in the remake of The Karate Kid.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4846340</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Robert Downey Jr.</name>
        <birthday>1965-04-04</birthday>
        <age>52</age>
        <biography>Robert John Downey Jr. (born April 4, 1965)[2] is an American actor. His career has included critical and popular success in his youth, followed by a period of substance abuse and legal troubles, and a resurgence of commercial success in middle age. For three consecutive years from 2012 to 2015, Downey has topped the Forbes list of Hollywood's highest-paid actors, making an estimated $80 million in earnings between June 2014 and June 2015.[3][4]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3498820</movie>
            <movie>tt2250912</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Donald Glover</name>
        <birthday>1983-09-25</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Donald McKinley Glover[1] (/ˈɡlʌvər/; born September 25, 1983) is an American actor, writer, producer, director, comedian, rapper, singer, and songwriter. As a recording artist, he usually performs under the stage name Childish Gambino, and as a disc jockey, he performs under the name mcDJ.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3778644</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>David Wenham</name>
        <birthday>1965-09-21</birthday>
        <age>52</age>
        <biography>David Wenham (born 21 September 1965) is an Australian actor who has appeared in movies, television series and theatre productions. He is known in Hollywood for his roles as Faramir in The Lord of the Rings film trilogy, Carl in Van Helsing, Dilios in 300 and its sequel 300: Rise of an Empire and Neil Fletcher in Australia. He is also known in his native Australia for his role as Diver Dan in SeaChange.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1790809</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Katherine Heigl</name>
        <birthday>1978-11-24</birthday>
        <age>39</age>
        <biography>Katherine Marie Heigl (/ˈhaɪɡəl/;[1] born November 24, 1978)[2] is an American actress, film producer and former fashion model. She played Izzie Stevens on ABC's medical drama Grey's Anatomy from 2005 to 2010, a role for which she won the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series in 2007. Heigl has also had a prominent film career, with appearances in Knocked Up (2007), 27 Dresses (2008), The Ugly Truth (2009), Killers (2010), Life As We Know It (2010) and New Year's Eve (2011). She played the lead role on the short-lived NBC television series State of Affairs from 2014 to 2015.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3462710</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dylan O'Brien</name>
        <birthday>1991-08-26</birthday>
        <age>26</age>
        <biography>Dylan O'Brien (born August 26, 1991) is an American actor and musician. He first received attention as "Stiles" Stilinski in the MTV series Teen Wolf,[2] and transitioned to film in projects such as The First Time, The Internship and Deepwater Horizon, and as the lead in the dystopian science-fiction adventure series The Maze Runner, consisting of The Maze Runner and its sequel, Maze Runner: The Scorch Trials. He is set to reprise his role in the final installment, Maze Runner: The Death Cure, which, after some re-scheduling due to a serious on-set accident concerning O'Brien, is scheduled for a January 12, 2018 release.[3][4]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4500922</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Meryl Streep</name>
        <birthday>1949-06-22</birthday>
        <age>68</age>
        <biography>Mary Louise "Meryl" Streep (born June 22, 1949) is an American actress and philanthropist. Cited in the media as the "best actress of her generation",[1][2][3] – a designation to which she objects[4] – Streep is particularly known for her versatility in her roles, transformation into the characters she plays, and her accent adaptation. Nominated for 20 Academy Awards, Streep has more nominations than any other actor or actress, and is one of the six actors to have won three or more competitive Oscars for acting. Streep has also received 30 Golden Globe nominations, winning eight—more nominations, and more competitive wins than any actor or actress.[5]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5028340</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Shohreh Aghdashloo</name>
        <birthday>1952-05-11</birthday>
        <age>65</age>
        <biography>Shohreh Aghdashloo (Persian: شهره آغداشلو‎‎, pronounced [ʃohˈɾe ɒɢdɒʃˈluː]; born May 11, 1952) is an Iranian-American actress. Following numerous starring roles on the stage, her first major film role was in The Report (Gozāresh) (1977) directed by Abbas Kiarostami, which won the Critics Award at the Moscow Film Festival. Her next film was Shatranje Bad (Chess of the Wind), directed by Mohammad Reza Aslani, which screened at several film festivals. Both films were banned in her home country; but, in 1978, Aghdashloo won acclaim for her performance in Sooteh Delan (Broken-Hearted), directed by Ali Hatami, which established her as one of Iran's leading actresses.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4776998</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Brendan Gleeson</name>
        <birthday>1955-03-29</birthday>
        <age>62</age>
        <biography>Brendan Gleeson (born 29 March 1955) is an Irish actor. He is the recipient of three IFTA Awards, two BIFA Awards, one Emmy Award and has been nominated twice for a BAFTA Award and three times for a Golden Globe Award.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2094766</movie>
            <movie>tt2361317</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Emily Blunt</name>
        <birthday>1983-02-23</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Emily Olivia Leah Blunt (born 23 February 1983)[2] is a British-American film and stage actress.[3] Blunt made her professional debut in a 2001 London production of the play The Royal Family. Two years later, she appeared on screen for the first time in the 2003 television film Boudica (Warrior Queen). Her performance in the 2004 drama film My Summer of Love garnered her the Evening Standard British Film Award for Most Promising Newcomer.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3631112</movie>
            <movie>tt5028340</movie>
            <movie>tt2296777</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sara Canning</name>
        <birthday>1987-07-14</birthday>
        <age>30</age>
        <biography>Sara Canning (born July 14, 1987) is a Canadian actress. She co-starred on The CW television series The Vampire Diaries as Jenna Sommers, and appeared in the 2009 feature film, Black Field. She starred as Dylan Weir in the Canadian television series, Primeval: New World, and as Dr. Melissa Conner on the Global medical drama Remedy.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3450958</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Timothy Radford</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1730768</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ellen Wong</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4255304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sebastian Stan</name>
        <birthday>1982-08-13</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Sebastian Stan (born August 13, 1982) is a Romanian-American[1] actor, known for his role as Bucky Barnes / Winter Soldier in the Marvel Cinematic Universe. On television, Stan portrayed Carter Baizen in Gossip Girl, Prince Jack Benjamin in Kings, Jefferson in Once Upon a Time, and T.J. Hammond in the miniseries Political Animals. His role in Political Animals earned him a nomination for the Critics' Choice Television Award for Best Supporting Actor in a Movie/Miniseries. In 2015, he co-starred in Jonathan Demme's Ricki and the Flash, Ridley Scott's The Martian, and Bryan Buckley's The Bronze.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3498820</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bobby Cannavale</name>
        <birthday>1970-05-03</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Robert "Bobby" Cannavale (/ˌkænəˈvɑːli/; Italian: [kannaˈvaːle]; born May 3, 1970)[1] is an American actor known for his leading role as Bobby Caffey in the first two seasons of the crime drama series Third Watch. Cannavale also had a recurring role on the NBC comedy series Will &amp; Grace as Will Truman's long-term boyfriend Officer Vincent "Vince" D'Angelo, for which he won the 2005 Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Guest Actor in a Comedy Series, and portrayed Gyp Rosetti during the third season of the HBO drama series Boardwalk Empire, for which he won the 2013 Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series. In 2016, he starred in the HBO drama series Vinyl, produced by Martin Scorsese and Mick Jagger.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1302006</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rachel House</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3521164</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Vin Diesel</name>
        <birthday>1967-07-18</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Mark Sinclair[1][2] (born July 18, 1967), better known by his stage name Vin Diesel, is an American actor, producer, director and screenwriter. He is well known for his portrayals of Dominic Toretto in The Fast and the Furious film series, Richard B. Riddick in The Chronicles of Riddick series and Xander Cage in the xXx series. He was also a producer on sequels in these franchises.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4630562</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Pitt</name>
        <birthday>1981-04-10</birthday>
        <age>36</age>
        <biography>Michael Carmen Pitt (born April 10, 1981) is an American actor, model and musician. Pitt is known in film for his roles in Bernardo Bertolucci's The Dreamers (2003), Gus Van Sant's Last Days (2005), Michael Haneke's Funny Games (2007) and M. Night Shyamalan's The Village (2004), and in television for his roles as Henry Parker in the teen drama Dawson's Creek, Jimmy Darmody in the HBO series Boardwalk Empire and Mason Verger in the NBC series Hannibal. He has also appeared in the films Hedwig and the Angry Inch (2001), Bully (2001), Silk (2007), Seven Psychopaths (2012) and I Origins (2014). His most recent appearance is in the film Ghost in the Shell (2017).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1219827</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jessica Chastain</name>
        <birthday>1977-03-24</birthday>
        <age>40</age>
        <biography>Jessica Michelle Chastain (born March 24, 1977)[a] is an American actress and film producer. Born in a small town near Sonoma, California,[a] and raised in Sacramento, Chastain developed an interest in acting from a young age. In 1998, she made her professional stage debut as Shakespeare's Juliet. After studying acting at the Juilliard School, she was signed to a talent holding deal with the television producer John Wells. She was a recurring guest star in several television shows, including Law &amp; Order: Trial by Jury. She also took on roles in the stage productions of Anton Chekhov's play The Cherry Orchard in 2004 and Oscar Wilde's tragedy Salome in 2006.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1730768</movie>
            <movie>tt4042818</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Christian Bale</name>
        <birthday>1974-01-30</birthday>
        <age>43</age>
        <biography>Christian Charles Philip Bale (born 30 January 1974) is an English actor.[3][4] He has starred both in blockbuster films and smaller projects from independent producers and art houses.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4776998</movie>
            <movie>tt2388771</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tom Cruise</name>
        <birthday>1962-07-03</birthday>
        <age>55</age>
        <biography>Thomas Cruise Mapother IV (born July 3, 1962), known professionally as Tom Cruise, is an American actor and producer. He has been nominated for three Academy Awards and has won three Golden Globe Awards. He started his career at age 19 in the film Endless Love (1981). After portraying supporting roles in Taps (1981) and The Outsiders (1983), his first leading role was in the romantic comedy Risky Business, released in August 1983. Cruise became a full-fledged movie star after starring as Pete "Maverick" Mitchell in the action drama Top Gun (1986). One of the biggest movie stars in Hollywood,[2][3] Cruise starred in several more successful films in the 1980s, including the dramas The Color of Money (1986), Cocktail (1988), Rain Man (1988), and Born on the Fourth of July (1989).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2345759</movie>
            <movie>tt4912910</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Scarlett Johansson</name>
        <birthday>1984-11-22</birthday>
        <age>33</age>
        <biography>Scarlett Johansson (/dʒoʊˈhænsən/; born November 22, 1984) is an American actress, model and singer. She made her film debut in the fantasy comedy North (1994). Johansson subsequently starred in Manny &amp; Lo (1996), and garnered further acclaim and prominence with roles in The Horse Whisperer (1998) and Ghost World (2001). She shifted to adult roles with her performances in Girl with a Pearl Earring (2003) and Lost in Translation (2003), for which she won a BAFTA Award for Best Actress in a Leading Role.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3470600</movie>
            <movie>tt3498820</movie>
            <movie>tt1219827</movie>
            <movie>tt4154756</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ben Affleck</name>
        <birthday>1972-08-15</birthday>
        <age>45</age>
        <biography>Benjamin Geza Affleck-Boldt (born August 15, 1972) is an American actor and filmmaker. He has received accolades including two Academy Awards, three Golden Globe Awards, two BAFTA Awards and two Screen Actors Guild Awards. He began acting as a child and starred in the PBS educational series The Voyage of the Mimi (1984, 1988). He later appeared in the independent coming-of-age comedy Dazed and Confused (1993) and various Kevin Smith films including Chasing Amy (1997) and Dogma (1999). Affleck gained recognition when he and childhood friend Matt Damon won the Golden Globe and Academy Award for Best Original Screenplay for Good Will Hunting (1997). He then established himself as a leading man in studio films including the disaster drama Armageddon (1998), the war drama Pearl Harbor (2001) and the thriller Changing Lanes (2002).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2975590</movie>
            <movie>tt2361317</movie>
            <movie>tt2140479</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Evangeline Lilly</name>
        <birthday>1979-08-03</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Nicole Evangeline Lilly (born August 3, 1979)[1][2] is a Canadian actress and author. She won a Screen Actors Guild Award and received a Golden Globe nomination for her role as Kate Austen in the ABC series Lost (2004–10).[3] She is also best known for her roles as Tauriel in The Hobbit,[4][5] Hope van Dyne in Ant-Man and Connie James in The Hurt Locker.[6][7]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5095030</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Raymond Ochoa</name>
        <birthday>2001-10-12</birthday>
        <age>16</age>
        <biography>Raymond Ochoa (born October 12, 2001) is an American child actor and voice actor. He has appeared in various commercials, television shows and movies including roles in 10 Items or Less, Merry Christmas, Drake &amp; Josh, and the lead character, Arlo, in the Pixar film The Good Dinosaur.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3606756</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tim McGraw</name>
        <birthday>1967-05-01</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Samuel Timothy "Tim" McGraw (born May 1, 1967) is an American singer, songwriter and actor. He has been married to singer Faith Hill since 1996, and is the son of the late baseball player Tug McGraw.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2872518</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Matthew McConaughey</name>
        <birthday>1969-11-04</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Matthew David McConaughey (/məˈkɒnəheɪ/;[3] born November 4, 1969)[4] is an American actor. He first gained notice for his breakout role in the coming-of-age comedy Dazed and Confused (1993). He appeared in such films as the slasher Texas Chainsaw Massacre: The Next Generation (1994), the legal thriller A Time to Kill (1996), Steven Spielberg's historical drama Amistad (1997), the science fiction drama Contact (1997), the comedy EDtv (1999), and the war film U-571 (2000).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3470600</movie>
            <movie>tt1648190</movie>
            <movie>tt4537896</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Cameron Monaghan</name>
        <birthday>1993-08-16</birthday>
        <age>24</age>
        <biography>Cameron Riley Monaghan (born August 16, 1993) is an American actor and model. Beginning with his professional career as a child model at the age of three, and child actor at the age of seven, Monaghan is best known for his role as Ian Gallagher on the Showtime comedy-drama (dramedy) series Shameless. He has also appeared as Kevin O'Doyle in Click (2006), Chad in the Fox comedy series Malcolm in the Middle, Corey Doyle in Prom (2011), Mason Ashford in Vampire Academy (2014), Asher in The Giver (2014), and as Jerome Valeska in the Fox crime series Gotham.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6054710</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ezra Miller</name>
        <birthday>1992-09-30</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Ezra Matthew Miller[1][2] (born September 30, 1992)[3][4][5] is an American actor, singer, musician and activist. He made his feature film debut in the film Afterschool (2008). He starred as the title character in the drama We Need to Talk About Kevin (2011) and co-starred in the film adaptation of The Perks of Being a Wallflower (2012). In 2015, he co-starred in the drama The Stanford Prison Experiment and in the comedy Trainwreck. He also plays Barry Allen / The Flash in the DC Extended Universe where he first appeared as Flash in Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice (2016) and also played Credence Barebone in Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4123430</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Mahershala Ali</name>
        <birthday>1974-02-16</birthday>
        <age>43</age>
        <biography>Mahershalalhashbaz "Mahershala" Ali (pronunciation: /məˈhɜːrʃələ/; born Mahershalalhashbaz Gilmore; February 16, 1974) is an American actor and rapper. Ali began his career as a regular on series such as Crossing Jordan and Threat Matrix before his breakthrough role as Richard Tyler in the science-fiction series The 4400. His first major film release was in the 2008 David Fincher-directed romantic fantasy drama film The Curious Case of Benjamin Button, and his other notable films include Predators, The Place Beyond the Pines, Free State of Jones, Hidden Figures and as Boggs in The Hunger Games series. Ali is also known for his roles in the Netflix series House of Cards as Remy Danton and as Cornell 'Cottonmouth' Stokes in Luke Cage.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4975722</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sterling K. Brown</name>
        <birthday>1976-04-05</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Sterling Kelby Brown (born April 5, 1976) is an American actor. He is known for playing Christopher Darden in The People v. O. J. Simpson: American Crime Story, for which he won the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Limited Series or Movie. Brown is also known for his role as Roland Burton on the Lifetime Network drama series Army Wives. He currently stars as Randall Pearson on the critically acclaimed NBC drama, This Is Us.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1825683</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ryan Gosling</name>
        <birthday>1980-11-12</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Ryan Thomas Gosling (born November 12, 1980)[1] is a Canadian actor and musician. He began his career as a child star on the Disney Channel's Mickey Mouse Club (1993–95) and went on to appear in other family entertainment programs including Are You Afraid of the Dark? (1995) and Goosebumps (1996). His first starring film role was as a Jewish neo-Nazi in The Believer (2001), and he went on to star in several independent films, including Murder by Numbers (2002), The Slaughter Rule (2002), and The United States of Leland (2003).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3783958</movie>
            <movie>tt1856101</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Janet Montgomery</name>
        <birthday>1985-10-29</birthday>
        <age>32</age>
        <biography>Janet Ruth Montgomery (born 29 October 1985) is an English film and TV actress. She is known for her role as Ames in the second season of Fox's Human Target,[1] and also for her appearances in The Hills Run Red and Wrong Turn 3: Left for Dead, as well as her role as Eric Murphy's assistant Jennie in HBO's Entourage. She recently played protagonist Martina Garretti in the short-lived Made in Jersey. As of 2014[update], she stars as the lead character, Mary Sibley, in the WGN America series, Salem. She is also known for her role as the mother of Gardner Elliot, Sarah Elliot in the 2017 film The Space Between Us.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3922818</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Channing Tatum</name>
        <birthday>1980-04-26</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Channing Matthew Tatum (born April 26, 1980)[1][2] is an American actor, dancer, and former stripper. Tatum made his film debut in the drama film Coach Carter (2005). His breakthrough role was in the 2006 dance film Step Up, which introduced him to a wider audience. He is known for his portrayal of the character Duke in the 2009 action film G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra and its 2013 sequel G.I. Joe: Retaliation. Although both G.I. Joe films received negative reviews from critics, they were commercially successful, grossing more than $300 million at the box office.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4649466</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Reese Witherspoon</name>
        <birthday>1976-03-22</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Laura Jeanne Reese Witherspoon (/ˈriːs ˈwɪðərspuːn/; born March 22, 1976) is an American actress, producer, and entrepreneur. Born in New Orleans and raised in Tennessee, she began her career as a child actress, making her professional screen debut in The Man in the Moon (1991), for which she was nominated for a Young Artist Award. Following breakout roles in Desperate Choices: To Save My Child (1992) and Jack the Bear, she starred in the comedy-drama Pleasantville (1998), for which she won the Young Hollywood Award for Breakthrough Performance. Her leading role of Tracy Flick in Election (1999) was nominated for a Golden Globe Award.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3470600</movie>
            <movie>tt1620680</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dicky Eklund Jr.</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4572514</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Stephen Lang</name>
        <birthday>1952-07-11</birthday>
        <age>65</age>
        <biography>Stephen Lang (born July 11, 1952) is an American actor and playwright. He started in Broadway theatre, but is more widely known for his film roles in Gods and Generals (2003), Avatar (2009), and Don't Breathe (2016). From 2004 to 2006, he was a co–artistic director of the Actors Studio.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4160708</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Holly Hunter</name>
        <birthday>1958-03-20</birthday>
        <age>59</age>
        <biography>Holly Hunter (born March 20, 1958) is an American actress and producer. For her performance as Ada McGrath in the 1993 film The Piano, she won the Academy Award for Best Actress, BAFTA Award for Best Actress in a Leading Role, AACTA Award for Best Actress in a Leading Role, Golden Globe Award for Best Actress – Motion Picture Drama, and the Cannes Best Actress Award. She was also nominated for the Academy Award for Best Actress for Broadcast News (1987), and the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress for The Firm (1993) and Thirteen (2003).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3606756</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Katheryn Winnick</name>
        <birthday>1977-12-17</birthday>
        <age>40</age>
        <biography>Katheryn Winnick (December 17, 1977[1][not in citation given]) is a Canadian actress. She is best known for her roles in Amusement (2008), Bones (2010), A Glimpse Inside the Mind of Charles Swan III (2012), Vikings (2013–present), and The Art of the Steal (2013).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1648190</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kevin Costner</name>
        <birthday>1955-01-18</birthday>
        <age>62</age>
        <biography>Kevin Michael Costner (born January 18, 1955) is an American actor, director, producer, and musician. His accolades include two Academy Awards, three Golden Globe Awards, and one Emmy Award.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4846340</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Andrew Garfield</name>
        <birthday>1983-08-20</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Andrew Russell Garfield (born 20 August 1983)[2][3] is a British American actor.[4][5][6][7] Born in Los Angeles and raised in Epsom, Surrey, Garfield began his career on the UK stage and in television productions. He made his feature-film debut in the 2007 ensemble drama Lions for Lambs. Garfield first came to international attention in 2010 with supporting roles in the drama films The Social Network, for which he received Golden Globe and BAFTA nominations for his portrayal of Eduardo Saverin, and Never Let Me Go, for which he received a Saturn Award and another BAFTA nomination.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2119532</movie>
            <movie>tt0490215</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Lucy Walters</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4814760</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Remo Girone</name>
        <birthday>1948-12-01</birthday>
        <age>69</age>
        <biography>Remo Girone (born 1948 in Asmara, Eritrea) is an Italian film and stage actor. He is best known for the role of Tano Cariddi in the epic TV mini-series La Piovra (The Octopus), about the Mafia. As a Mafia leader, Tano's chief enemies were Commissario (police commissioner) Corrado Cattani and Giudice (judge) Silvia Conti. He appeared as an Italian-American mob boss in Ben Affleck's crime drama Live by Night, which was released in December 2016.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2361317</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Whitney Cummings</name>
        <birthday>1982-09-04</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Whitney Cummings (born September 4, 1982)[1] is an American comedian and actress. She is known as the creator and star of the NBC sitcom Whitney, as well as the co-creator of the CBS sitcom 2 Broke Girls.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3462710</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Noomi Rapace</name>
        <birthday>1979-12-28</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Noomi Rapace (Swedish pronunciation: [ˈnoːmɪ raˈpɑːs];[1] née Norén; born 28 December 1979) is a Swedish actress.[2] She achieved fame with her portrayal of Lisbeth Salander in the Swedish film adaptations of the Millennium series: The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo, The Girl Who Played with Fire, and The Girl Who Kicked the Hornets' Nest.[3] In 2011, she was nominated for a BAFTA Award for Best Actress for her performance in The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2316204</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Derrick Gilbert</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1502397</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Juliette Binoche</name>
        <birthday>1964-03-09</birthday>
        <age>53</age>
        <biography>Juliette Binoche (French pronunciation: ​[ʒyljɛt binɔʃ]; born 9 March 1964) is a French actress, artist and dancer. She has appeared in more than 60 feature films, been recipient of numerous international awards, and has appeared on stage and in movies across the world. Coming from an artistic background, she began taking acting lessons during adolescence. After performing in several stage productions, she began acting in films by auteur directors Jean-Luc Godard (Hail Mary, 1985), Jacques Doillon (Family Life, 1985) and André Téchiné, who made her a star in France with the leading role in his 1985 drama Rendez-vous. Her sensual performance in her English-language debut The Unbearable Lightness of Being (1988), directed by Philip Kaufman, launched her international career.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1219827</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Haley Lu Richardson</name>
        <birthday>1995-03-07</birthday>
        <age>22</age>
        <biography>Haley Lu Richardson (born March 7, 1995) is an American actress. She may be best known for her role as Krista in the film The Edge of Seventeen.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4972582</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bill Murray</name>
        <birthday>1950-09-21</birthday>
        <age>67</age>
        <biography>William James "Bill" Murray (born September 21, 1950) is an American actor, comedian, and writer. He first gained exposure on Saturday Night Live, a role that earned him his first Emmy Award, and later starred in comedy films—including Meatballs (1979), Caddyshack (1980), Stripes (1981), Tootsie (1982), Ghostbusters (1984), Scrooged (1988), Ghostbusters II (1989), What About Bob? (1991), and Groundhog Day (1993). He also co-directed Quick Change (1990).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5104604</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Peña</name>
        <birthday>1976-01-13</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Michael Anthony Peña (born January 13, 1976) is an American actor and musician. He has starred in many films, such as Crash (2004), World Trade Center (2006), Shooter (2007), Observe and Report (2009), Tower Heist (2011), Battle: Los Angeles (2011), End of Watch (2012), Gangster Squad (2013), American Hustle (2013), Fury (2014), Ant-Man (2015), and The Martian (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4682786</movie>
            <movie>tt0493405</movie>
            <movie>tt1620680</movie>
            <movie>tt5095030</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Radha Mitchell</name>
        <birthday>1973-11-12</birthday>
        <age>44</age>
        <biography>Radha Rani Amber Indigo Ananda Mitchell (born 12 November 1973) is an Australian actress. She started her career acting in various Australian TV series and films, and later appeared in Hollywood films such as Pitch Black, Phone Booth, Finding Neverland, Man on Fire, Melinda and Melinda, Silent Hill and The Crazies.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2872518</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Daisy Ridley</name>
        <birthday>1992-04-10</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Daisy Jazz Isobel Ridley (born 10 April 1992) is an English actress. She began her acting career by appearing in minor television roles and short films before being cast in the lead role of Rey in the Star Wars sequel trilogy, first appearing in Star Wars: The Force Awakens (2015). In 2017, she will reprise her role as Rey in Star Wars: The Last Jedi.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2527336</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Billy MacLellan</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3721954</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Liam Neeson</name>
        <birthday>1952-06-07</birthday>
        <age>65</age>
        <biography>Liam John Neeson, OBE, (born 7 June 1952)[2] is an actor from Northern Ireland.[3] In 1976, he joined the Lyric Players' Theatre in Belfast for two years. He then acted in the Arthurian film, Excalibur (1981). Between 1982 and 1987, Neeson starred in five films; most notably alongside Mel Gibson and Anthony Hopkins in The Bounty (1984) and Robert De Niro and Jeremy Irons in The Mission (1986). He landed a leading role alongside Patrick Swayze in Next of Kin (1989).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0490215</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Allison Williams</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5052448</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jason Segel</name>
        <birthday>1980-01-18</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Jason Jordan Segel (/ˈsiːɡəl/; born January 18, 1980) is an American actor, screenwriter, comedian, producer, and author, best known for his role as Marshall Eriksen in the CBS sitcom How I Met Your Mother, as well as for his work with producer Judd Apatow on the television series Freaks and Geeks and Undeclared, and for the critically and commercially successful comedies he's starred in, written and produced.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5155780</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Finn Wolfhard</name>
        <birthday>2002-12-23</birthday>
        <age>15</age>
        <biography>Finn Wolfhard is a Canadian actor. He is best known for his starring role as Mike Wheeler in the supernatural Netflix hit TV series Stranger Things.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1396484</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Stephanie Sigman</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5140878</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Malin Akerman</name>
        <birthday>1978-05-12</birthday>
        <age>39</age>
        <biography>Malin Maria Åkerman (Swedish pronunciation: [ˈmɑːlɪn ²oːkɛrˌman],[1] English pronunciation: /ˈmɑːlɪn ˈækərmæn/; born May 12, 1978)[2] is a Swedish Canadian actress, model and singer. She became known for making appearances in several Canadian productions. In the early 2000s, she had many television and film parts, including The Utopian Society (2003) and Harold &amp; Kumar Go to White Castle (2004). Following a supporting role on the comedy series The Comeback (2005), Åkerman gained her first starring roles in the feature films The Heartbreak Kid (2007) and 27 Dresses (2008).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2231461</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ralph Fiennes</name>
        <birthday>1962-12-22</birthday>
        <age>55</age>
        <biography>Ralph Nathaniel Twisleton-Wykeham-Fiennes (/ˈreɪf ˈfaɪnz/;[2] born 22 December 1962) is an English actor. A noted Shakespeare interpreter, he first achieved success onstage at the Royal National Theatre.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4116284</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Joe Manganiello</name>
        <birthday>1976-12-28</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Joseph Michael "Joe" Manganiello (/ˌmæŋɡəˈnɛloʊ/ MANG-gə-NEL-oh; Italian pronunciation: [maŋɡaˈnjɛllo]; born December 28, 1976) is an American actor, director, producer, author and philanthropist. He played Flash Thompson in Sam Raimi's Spider-Man trilogy and had various recurring roles in television on ER, How I Met Your Mother, and One Tree Hill, before landing his breakout role as werewolf Alcide Herveaux on the HBO television series True Blood. In 2011, he was voted "Favorite Pop-Culture Werewolf of All Time" by the readers of Entertainment Weekly, and one of Men's Health's "100 Fittest Men of All Time".[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2398241</movie>
            <movie>tt2231461</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Alicia Vela-Bailey</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5140878</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Halle Berry</name>
        <birthday>1966-08-14</birthday>
        <age>51</age>
        <biography>Halle Maria Berry (born Maria Halle Berry; August 14, 1966)[1] is an American actress. She won the 2002 Academy Award for Best Actress for her performance in the romantic drama Monster's Ball (2001). As of 2017, she is the only black woman to have won a Best Actress Academy Award.[2][3]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4649466</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bryce Dallas Howard</name>
        <birthday>1981-03-02</birthday>
        <age>36</age>
        <biography>Bryce Dallas Howard (born March 2, 1981) is an American film actress, director, producer, and writer. Howard attended New York University's Tisch School of the Arts, but would ultimately leave before graduating to take on roles on Broadway. During a performance of As You Like It where Howard portrayed Rosalind, she caught the attention of director M. Night Shyamalan, and he cast her in what would be her breakout film, the psychological thriller The Village (2004) and then in the fantasy thriller Lady in the Water (2006). Her performance in Kenneth Branagh’s film adaptation of As You Like It (2006) earned her a Golden Globe Award nomination. In 2006, she co-wrote and directed the short film Orchids.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4881806</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tom Hanks</name>
        <birthday>1956-07-09</birthday>
        <age>61</age>
        <biography>Thomas Jeffrey Hanks[2] (born July 9, 1956)[3][4] is an American actor and filmmaker. He is known for his various comedic and dramatic film roles, including Splash (1984), Big (1988), Turner &amp; Hooch (1989), A League of Their Own (1992), Sleepless in Seattle (1993), Philadelphia (1993), Forrest Gump (1994), Apollo 13 (1995), Saving Private Ryan (1998), You've Got Mail (1998), The Green Mile (1999), Cast Away (2000), Road to Perdition (2002), and The Da Vinci Code (2006), as well as for his voice work in the animated films The Polar Express (2004) and the Toy Story series.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4287320</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jason Bateman</name>
        <birthday>1969-01-14</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Jason Kent Bateman (born January 14, 1969) is an American actor, director and producer. He began acting on television in the early 1980s on Little House on the Prairie, and in the sitcoms Silver Spoons and The Hogan Family. In the 2000s, he became known for his role of Michael Bluth in the critically acclaimed sitcom Arrested Development, for which he won a Golden Globe, and a Satellite Award. He has had starring roles in the films, Juno (2007), Hancock (2008), Up in the Air (2009), The Switch (2010), Paul (2011), Horrible Bosses (2011), The Change-Up (2011), Identity Thief (2013), Bad Words (2013), Horrible Bosses 2 (2014), The Gift (2015), and Zootopia (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1711525</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Scott Takeda</name>
        <birthday>1967-03-21</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Scott Takeda (born March 21, 1967) is an American actor, filmmaker and photographer. His film roles include parts in Everything Must Go, Dallas Buyers Club and Gone Girl.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3922818</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Alex R. Hibbert</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4975722</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Olivia Cooke</name>
        <birthday>1993-12-27</birthday>
        <age>24</age>
        <biography>Olivia Kate Cooke[1] (born 27 December 1993) is an English actress. Since 2013, she has co-starred as Emma Decody in the A&amp;E drama-thriller television series Bates Motel. Prior to this, she appeared in two BBC miniseries, Blackout and The Secret of Crickley Hall. In 2014, Cooke starred in three supernatural thriller films: The Quiet Ones, The Signal, and Ouija. These roles have given her the reputation of a contemporary scream queen. In 2015, she portrayed Rachel Kushner in the comedy-drama Me and Earl and the Dying Girl.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1677720</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Logan Gillies</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2763304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kyle Chandler</name>
        <birthday>1965-09-17</birthday>
        <age>52</age>
        <biography>Kyle Martin Chandler (born September 17, 1965) is an American actor, best known for his roles on Early Edition and notably as Coach Eric Taylor in the drama series Friday Night Lights, for which he won a Primetime Emmy Award in 2011. He has starred in the films King Kong (2005), The Day the Earth Stood Still (2008), Super 8 (2011), Argo (2012), Zero Dark Thirty (2012), The Wolf of Wall Street (2013), Carol (2015), and Manchester by the Sea (2016).[1] In 2015, he began starring on Netflix's drama series Bloodline, for which he received his fourth and fifth Primetime Emmy Award nominations.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4034228</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Smiley</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4158096</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Aaron Poole</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4255304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Stanley Tucci</name>
        <birthday>1960-11-11</birthday>
        <age>57</age>
        <biography>Stanley Tucci (/ˈtuːtʃi/; Italian: [ˈtuttʃi]; born November 11, 1960)[1] is an American character actor,[2][3] writer, producer and film director.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3371366</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kate Beckinsale</name>
        <birthday>1973-07-26</birthday>
        <age>44</age>
        <biography>Kathrin Romary "Kate" Beckinsale (born 26 July 1973) is a British actress.[2] After some minor television roles, she made her film debut in Much Ado About Nothing (1993) while still a student at the University of Oxford. She then appeared in British costume dramas such as Prince of Jutland (1994), Cold Comfort Farm (1995), Emma (1996), and The Golden Bowl (2000), in addition to various stage and radio productions. She began to seek film work in the United States in the late 1990s and, after appearing in small-scale dramas The Last Days of Disco (1998) and Brokedown Palace (1999), she had starring roles in the war drama Pearl Harbor and the romantic comedy Serendipity. She followed those with appearances in The Aviator (2004) and Click (2006).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3717252</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rila Fukushima</name>
        <birthday>1989-01-16</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Rila Fukushima (福島 リラ, Fukushima Rira?, born January 16, 1989) is a Japanese fashion model and actress. She was born in Kyūshū and raised in Tokyo, Japan.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1219827</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Douglas Smith</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4030600</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Naomi Scott</name>
        <birthday>1993-05-06</birthday>
        <age>24</age>
        <biography>Naomi Grace Scott (born 6 May 1993) is an English actress and singer. She is known for starring as Kimberly Hart, the Pink Ranger, in the 2017 Power Rangers movie and co-starring as Maddy Shannon in the science-fiction drama series Terra Nova. Scott also starred as Mohini "Mo" Banjaree in the Disney Channel original movie Lemonade Mouth, and as Megan in TV series Life Bites.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3717490</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Adam Brody</name>
        <birthday>1979-12-15</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Adam Jared Brody (born December 15, 1979)[1] is an American actor, writer, musician and producer. He is best known for his role as Seth Cohen on The O.C..[2] Brody has appeared in the films Mr. &amp; Mrs. Smith (2005), Thank You for Smoking (2006), In the Land of Women (2007), Jennifer's Body (2009), Cop Out (2010), Scream 4 (2011), Lovelace (2013), Life Partners (2014), and Sleeping with Other People (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0493405</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Caine</name>
        <birthday>1933-03-14</birthday>
        <age>84</age>
        <biography>Sir Michael Caine, CBE (/keɪn/; born Maurice Joseph Micklewhite; 14 March 1933) is an English actor and author. Renowned for his distinctive working class cockney accent, Caine has appeared in over 115 films and is regarded as a British film icon.[2]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2568862</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Eric Johnson</name>
        <birthday>1954-08-17</birthday>
        <age>63</age>
        <biography>Eric Johnson (born August 17, 1954) is a guitarist from Austin, Texas. His album Ah Via Musicom (1990) was certified platinum by the RIAA and the single "Cliffs of Dover" won the Grammy Award for Best Rock Instrumental Performance.[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4465564</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Tim Bentinck</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3183660</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Katie McGrath</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1972591</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Cillian Murphy</name>
        <birthday>1976-05-25</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Cillian Murphy (/ˈkɪliən/; born 25 May 1976) is an Irish actor of stage and screen. Since making his debut in his home country in the late 1990s, Murphy has also become a presence in British and American cinemas noted by critics for his performances in many independent and mainstream films. He is best known as Jim in 28 Days Later (2002), the Scarecrow in The Dark Knight Trilogy (2005–12), Jackson Rippner in Red Eye (2005), Robert Capa in Sunshine (2007), Robert Fischer in Inception (2010) and Thomas Shelby in the BBC series Peaky Blinders.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5013056</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Judy Greer</name>
        <birthday>1975-07-20</birthday>
        <age>42</age>
        <biography>Judy Greer (born Judith Therese Evans; July 20, 1975)[1][2][3] is an American actress, model and author, known for several television and film roles. On television, her best known roles include Kitty Sanchez on Arrested Development, Ingrid Nelson/Fatty Magoo on It's Always Sunny In Philadelphia, Trixie on Californication, and Cheryl Tunt on the animated comedy series Archer. In film, Greer is known for several supporting roles in romantic comedies, with appearances in What Women Want (2000), The Wedding Planner (2001), 13 Going on 30 (2004), 27 Dresses (2008) and Love and Other Drugs (2010). Her other film appearances include roles in The Descendants (2011), Carrie (2013) and Jurassic World (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3450958</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jack McBrayer</name>
        <birthday>1973-05-27</birthday>
        <age>44</age>
        <biography>Jack McBrayer /ˌməkˈbrɛər/ (born May 27, 1973) is an American actor and comedian. He gained national exposure for his portrayal of characters in Late Night with Conan O'Brien and as Kenneth Parcell in 30 Rock, for which he was nominated for Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Comedy Series at the 61st Primetime Emmy Awards.[2] He has voiced characters in Wreck-it Ralph, Phineas and Ferb, and Wander Over Yonder, and currently plays Dr. Ted Goodwin, a recurring character on the ABC sitcom The Middle.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2398241</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Viola Davis</name>
        <birthday>1965-08-11</birthday>
        <age>52</age>
        <biography>Viola Davis (born August 11, 1965)[1] is an American actress and producer. She is the only black woman to be nominated for three Academy Awards, winning one, and is the only black actress or actor to win the Triple Crown of Acting.[2][3][4] In 2012, she was listed by Time Magazine as one of the 100 most influential people in the world.[5]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4218572</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Chris Sullivan</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3896198</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Will Arnett</name>
        <birthday>1970-05-04</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>William Emerson "Will" Arnett (/ɑːrˈnɛt/; born May 4, 1970)[1] is a Canadian-American actor, voice actor and comedian. He is known for his role as George Oscar "Gob" Bluth II in the Fox series Arrested Development and Devon Banks in the NBC series 30 Rock, for which he was nominated for five Emmy Awards. He also appeared in the IFC series The Increasingly Poor Decisions of Todd Margaret, the NBC series Up All Night, and the CBS series The Millers, and in films such as Monster-in-Law, Semi-Pro, Blades of Glory, RV, Hot Rod, Let's Go to Prison, The Rocker, Monsters vs. Aliens, The Brothers Solomon, When in Rome, Jonah Hex, The Lego Movie, The Nut Job, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, and Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Out of the Shadows. Arnett is also known for his voice acting - he voices the title character of Netflix's original animated series BoJack Horseman, and also portrays Batman in The Lego Movie and its spin-off The Lego Batman Movie. He currently stars in Netflix's Flaked.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4116284</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Amy Adams</name>
        <birthday>1974-08-20</birthday>
        <age>43</age>
        <biography>Amy Lou Adams (born August 20, 1974) is an American actress and singer. She was named one of 100 most influential people by Time magazine in 2014 and is among the highest-paid actresses in the world.[1] She has won two Golden Globe Awards and has been nominated for five Academy Awards, and six BAFTA Awards.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2543164</movie>
            <movie>tt4550098</movie>
            <movie>tt2975590</movie>
            <movie>tt0974015</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jon Favreau</name>
        <birthday>1966-10-19</birthday>
        <age>51</age>
        <biography>Jonathan Kolia "Jon" Favreau[1] (/ˈfævroʊ/; born October 19, 1966) is an American actor, filmmaker, and comedian.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2250912</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bryan Cranston</name>
        <birthday>1956-03-07</birthday>
        <age>61</age>
        <biography>Bryan Lee Cranston (born March 7, 1956)[1] is an American actor, screenwriter, director, producer, comedian and voice actor. He is best known for portraying Walter White on the AMC crime drama series Breaking Bad, Hal on the Fox comedy series Malcolm in the Middle, and Dr. Tim Whatley in five episodes of the NBC comedy series Seinfeld. For Breaking Bad, he won the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Lead Actor in a Drama Series four times (2008–2010, 2014), including three consecutive wins (the second time in television history after Bill Cosby in I Spy during the 1960s).[2] After becoming one of the producers of Breaking Bad in 2011, he also won the award for Outstanding Drama Series twice.[3]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1987680</movie>
            <movie>tt5104604</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Patrick Stewart</name>
        <birthday>1940-07-13</birthday>
        <age>77</age>
        <biography>Sir Patrick Stewart OBE (born 13 July 1940) is an English actor whose career has included roles on stage, television, and film in a career spanning almost six decades.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3315342</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Annie Ilonzeh</name>
        <birthday>1983-08-23</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Annette Ngosi "Annie" Ilonzeh (born August 23, 1983) is an American actress. She is known for her roles as Maya Ward on General Hospital and Kate Prince in the short-lived ABC reboot of Charlie's Angels.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1666185</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>John Goodman</name>
        <birthday>1952-06-20</birthday>
        <age>65</age>
        <biography>John Stephen Goodman (born June 20, 1952) is an American actor. Early in his career, he was best known for playing Dan Conner on the ABC TV series Roseanne (1988–1997), for which he won a Golden Globe Award for Best Actor in 1993. He is also a regular collaborator with the Coen brothers on such films as Raising Arizona (1987), Barton Fink (1991), The Big Lebowski (1998), O Brother, Where Art Thou? (2000), and Inside Llewyn Davis (2013). Goodman's voice roles in animated films include Pacha in Disney's The Emperor's New Groove (2000), and Sulley in Pixar's Monsters, Inc. (2001), and Monsters University (2013).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2239822</movie>
            <movie>tt2406566</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Keanu Reeves</name>
        <birthday>1964-09-02</birthday>
        <age>53</age>
        <biography>Keanu Charles Reeves (/kiːˈɑːnuː/ kee-AH-noo;[1] born September 2, 1964)[2][3] is a Canadian actor, producer, and musician. Reeves is best known for his acting career, beginning in 1985 and spanning more than three decades. He gained fame for his starring role performances in several blockbuster films including comedies from the Bill and Ted franchise (1989–1991), action thrillers Point Break (1991), Speed (1994), and the John Wick franchise, psychological thriller The Devil's Advocate (1997), the supernatural thriller Constantine (2005), and the science fiction-action trilogy The Matrix (1999–2003). He has also appeared in dramatic films such as Dangerous Liaisons (1988), My Own Private Idaho (1991), and Little Buddha (1993), as well as the romantic horror Bram Stoker's Dracula (1992).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4425200</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ewan McGregor</name>
        <birthday>1971-03-31</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Ewan Gordon McGregor OBE (/ˌjuːən məˈɡrɛɡər/; born 31 March 1971)[1] is a Scottish actor. His first professional role was in 1993, when he won a leading role in the Channel 4 series Lipstick on Your Collar.[2] He is known for playing heroin addict Mark Renton in the drama films Trainspotting (1996) and T2 Trainspotting (2017), the young Jedi Obi-Wan Kenobi in the Star Wars prequel trilogy (1999–2005), poet Christian in the musical film Moulin Rouge! (2001), Camerlengo Father Patrick McKenna in Angels and Demons (2009), Dr. Alfred Jones in the romantic comedy-drama Salmon Fishing in the Yemen (2011), and Lumière in a live-action adaptation of Beauty and the Beast (2017).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2763304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kat Graham</name>
        <birthday>1989-09-05</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Katerina Alexandre Hartford "Kat" Graham[1][2] (born September 5, 1989) is a Swiss-born American actress, model, singer and dancer. Her film roles include The Parent Trap (1998), 17 Again (2009), The Roommate (2011) and Honey 2 (2011). She is known for her role as Bonnie Bennett on The CW supernatural drama The Vampire Diaries.[3][4][5]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1666185</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ann-Margret</name>
        <birthday>1941-04-28</birthday>
        <age>76</age>
        <biography>Ann-Margret (born Ann-Margret Olsson; April 28, 1941) is a Swedish-American actress, singer, and dancer. As an actress, she is best known for her roles in Bye Bye Birdie (1963), Viva Las Vegas (1964), The Cincinnati Kid (1965), Carnal Knowledge (1971), Tommy (1975), Grumpy Old Men (1993), and Grumpier Old Men (1995). She has won five Golden Globe Awards and been nominated for two Academy Awards, two Grammy Awards, a Screen Actors Guild Award, and six Emmy Awards. In 2010, she won her first Emmy Award for her guest appearance on Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit. Her singing and acting careers span five decades, starting in 1961; initially, she was billed as a female version of Elvis Presley. She had a minor hit in 1961 and a charting album in 1964, and scored a disco hit in 1979. In 2001, she recorded a critically acclaimed gospel album, and an album of Christmas songs from 2004 continues to be available.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2568862</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Brian McCarthy</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5155780</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ryûnosuke Kamiki</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5311514</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Mary Steenburgen</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5155780</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ivo Nandi</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4731136</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Miranda Otto</name>
        <birthday>1967-12-16</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Miranda Otto (born 16 December 1967) is an Australian actress. The daughter of actors Barry and Lindsay Otto, and the sister of actress Gracie Otto, Brisbane-born Miranda began her acting career at age 18 in 1986, and has appeared in a variety of independent and major studio films. Otto made her major film debut in Emma's War, in which she played a teenager who moves to Australia's bush country during World War II.[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5140878</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Arnold Schwarzenegger</name>
        <birthday>1947-07-30</birthday>
        <age>70</age>
        <biography>Arnold Alois Schwarzenegger (/ˈʃwɔːrtsənˌɛɡər/; German: [ˈaɐ̯nɔlt ˈalɔʏs ˈʃvaɐ̯tsn̩ˌɛɡɐ]; born July 30, 1947) is an Austrian-American actor, producer, businessman, investor, author, philanthropist, activist, politician and former professional bodybuilder. He served two terms as the 38th Governor of California from 2003 until 2011.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4581576</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Riccardo Scamarcio</name>
        <birthday>1979-11-13</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Riccardo Scamarcio (born 13 November 1979) is an Italian film actor and film producer.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4425200</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Aoi Yuki</name>
        <birthday>1992-03-27</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Aoi Yabusaki (八武崎 碧, Yabusaki Aoi?, born March 27, 1992 in Chiba Prefecture), better known by her stage name Aoi Yūki (悠木 碧, Yūki Aoi?) is a Japanese actress, voice actress and singer represented by the Pro-Fit agency.[2]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5311514</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Guy Pearce</name>
        <birthday>1967-10-05</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Guy Edward Pearce (born 5 October 1967)[1] is an Australian actor and musician.[2] He is well known for having starred in the role of Mike Young in the Australian television series Neighbours and in films such as The Adventures of Priscilla, Queen of the Desert (1994), L.A. Confidential (1997), Memento (2000), The Count of Monte Cristo (2002), The Road (2009), The King's Speech (2010), Prometheus (2012), and Iron Man 3 (2013). In Australian cinema, he has appeared in The Proposition (2005), Animal Kingdom (2010), The Rover (2014), Holding the Man (2015) and The Wizards of Aus (2016). He has won an Emmy Award and received nominations for Golden Globe Awards, Screen Actors Guild Awards, and AACTA Awards. Since 2012 he has played the title role in the TV adaptations of the Jack Irish stories by Australian crime writer Peter Temple.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1895315</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Mike Vogel</name>
        <birthday>1979-07-17</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Michael James "Mike" Vogel[1] (born July 17, 1979) is an American actor and former model. Vogel began acting in 2001, and has since appeared in several films and series, including The Texas Chainsaw Massacre, The Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants, Grind, Poseidon, Blue Valentine, The Help, Bates Motel, Cloverfield and Under the Dome.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6113488</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ana de Armas</name>
        <birthday>1988-04-30</birthday>
        <age>29</age>
        <biography>Ana Celia de Armas Caso (born 30 April 1988) is a Cuban actress.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1856101</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Willem Dafoe</name>
        <birthday>1955-07-22</birthday>
        <age>62</age>
        <biography>William J. "Willem" Dafoe (born July 22, 1955) is an American actor. A member of the experimental theatre company the Wooster Group, he was nominated for the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for his roles as Elias in Oliver Stone's Platoon (1986) and Max Schreck in the comedy-horror film Shadow of the Vampire (2000). His other film appearances include The Last Temptation of Christ (1988), The English Patient (1996), American Psycho (2000), the Spider-Man trilogy (2002–2007) and Justice League (2017). He has also had voice roles in Finding Nemo (2003) and it's sequel Finding Dory (2016), Fantastic Mr. Fox (2009) and the forthcoming adaptation of Death Note (2017).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2034800</movie>
            <movie>tt1477834</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Amber Heard</name>
        <birthday>1986-04-22</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Amber Laura Heard (born April 22, 1986)[1] is an American actress. She made her film debut in 2004 in the sports drama Friday Night Lights, starring Billy Bob Thornton. After small roles in North Country and Alpha Dog, Heard played her first leading role in All the Boys Love Mandy Lane (2006) and appeared in The CW television show Hidden Palms (2007).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1477834</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Benyaer</name>
        <birthday>1970-05-25</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Michael Benyaer (born May 25, 1970) is a Canadian/American actor, cartoon and video game voice actor and is probably best known for his roles as Bob in the Canadian CGI series ReBoot, seasons 1, 2 and 4 and Hadji Singh in season one of The Real Adventures of Jonny Quest.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1431045</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dax Shepard</name>
        <birthday>1975-01-02</birthday>
        <age>42</age>
        <biography>Dax Randall Shepard (born January 2, 1975) is an American actor, writer and director. He is best known for his work in the feature films Employee of the Month (2006), Without a Paddle (2004), Idiocracy (2006), Let's Go to Prison (2006), Hit and Run (2012), and CHiPs (2017), the last pair of which he also wrote and directed, and the MTV practical joke reality series Punk'd (2003). He portrayed Crosby Braverman in the NBC comedy-drama series Parenthood from 2010 to 2015.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0493405</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Nicole Kidman</name>
        <birthday>1967-06-20</birthday>
        <age>50</age>
        <biography>Nicole Mary Kidman, AC (born 20 June 1967) is an Australian actress and film producer.[4] Kidman's breakthrough roles were in the 1989 feature film thriller Dead Calm and television thriller miniseries Bangkok Hilton. Appearing in several films in the early 1990s, she came to worldwide recognition for her performances in the stock-car racing film Days of Thunder (1990), the romance-drama Far and Away (1992), and the superhero film Batman Forever (1995). Other successful films followed in the late 1990s. Her performance in the musical Moulin Rouge! (2001) earned her a second Golden Globe Award for Best Actress – Motion Picture Comedy or Musical and her first nomination for the Academy Award for Best Actress. Kidman's performance as Virginia Woolf in the drama film The Hours (2002) received critical acclaim and earned her the Academy Award for Best Actress, the BAFTA Award for Best Actress in a Leading Role, the Golden Globe Award for Best Actress in a Motion Picture – Drama and the Silver Bear for Best Actress at the Berlin International Film Festival.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1987680</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Zooey Deschanel</name>
        <birthday>1980-01-17</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Zooey Claire Deschanel (/ˈzoʊi ˌdeɪʃəˈnɛl/; born January 17, 1980) is an American actress and singer-songwriter. She made her film debut in Mumford (1999), followed by her supporting role in Cameron Crowe's semi-autobiographical picture Almost Famous (2000). Deschanel soon became known for her deadpan comedy roles in films such as The Good Girl (2002), The New Guy (2002), Elf (2003), The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy (2005), Failure to Launch (2006), Yes Man (2008), and (500) Days of Summer (2009).[1][2][3] She also did dramatic turns in the films Manic (2001), All the Real Girls (2003), Winter Passing (2005) and Bridge to Terabithia (2007).[4][5] Since 2011, she has played Jessica Day on the Fox sitcom New Girl, for which she has received an Emmy Award nomination and three Golden Globe Award nominations.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1679335</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Olivia Munn</name>
        <birthday>1980-07-03</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Lisa Olivia Munn (born July 3, 1980)[1][2] is an American actress and model. She was credited as Lisa Munn in her early career, but since 2006, she has used the name Olivia Munn.[3]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1711525</movie>
            <movie>tt5164214</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Erika Christensen</name>
        <birthday>1982-08-19</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Erika Jane Christensen (born August 19, 1982)[1] is an American actress and singer whose filmography includes roles in Traffic (2000), Swimfan (2002), The Banger Sisters (2002), The Perfect Score (2004), Flightplan (2005), How to Rob a Bank (2007), The Tortured (2010), and The Case for Christ (2017). For her performance in Traffic, she won the MTV Movie Award for Breakthrough Female Performance and the Screen Actors Guild Award for Outstanding Performance by a Cast in a Motion Picture along with her co-stars.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6113488</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Stuhlbarg</name>
        <birthday>1968-07-05</birthday>
        <age>49</age>
        <biography>Michael Stuhlbarg (/ˈstuːlˌbɑːrɡ/; born July 5, 1968)[1] is an American actor. He played troubled university professor Larry Gopnik in the 2009 dark comedy film A Serious Man, organized-crime boss Arnold Rothstein in the HBO television series Boardwalk Empire (2010–2013), Griffin in Men in Black 3 (2012), Dr. Flicker in Blue Jasmine (2013), and computer scientist and inventor Andy Hertzfeld in the biopic Steve Jobs (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2543164</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Shane West</name>
        <birthday>1978-06-10</birthday>
        <age>39</age>
        <biography>Shane West (born Shannon Bruce Snaith;[1] June 10, 1978) is an American actor, punk rock musician and songwriter. West is known for his portrayal of Eli Sammler in the ABC family drama Once and Again, Landon Carter in A Walk to Remember, Darby Crash in What We Do Is Secret, Dr. Ray Barnett in the NBC medical drama ER and Michael Bishop in The CW spy drama Nikita. He also starred in the WGN adventure/historical/fantasy drama Salem as John Alden.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4814760</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Edward Norton</name>
        <birthday>1969-08-18</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Edward Harrison Norton (born August 18, 1969) is an American actor, filmmaker and activist. He has been nominated for three Academy Awards for his work in the films Primal Fear (1996), American History X (1998) and Birdman (2014). He also starred in other roles, such as Everyone Says I Love You (1996), The People vs. Larry Flynt (1996), Fight Club (1999), Red Dragon (2002), 25th Hour (2002), Kingdom of Heaven (2005), The Illusionist (2006), Moonrise Kingdom (2012), The Grand Budapest Hotel (2014) and Sausage Party (2016). He has also directed and co-written films, including his directorial debut, Keeping the Faith (2000). He has done uncredited work on the scripts for The Score (2001), Frida (2002), and The Incredible Hulk (2008).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4682786</movie>
            <movie>tt5104604</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Bradley Whitford</name>
        <birthday>1959-10-10</birthday>
        <age>58</age>
        <biography>Bradley Whitford (born October 10, 1959) is an actor. He has played White House Deputy Chief of Staff Josh Lyman on the NBC television drama The West Wing, Danny Tripp on Studio 60 on the Sunset Strip, Dan Stark in the Fox police buddy-comedy The Good Guys, Timothy Carter, a character who was believed to be Red John, in the CBS series The Mentalist, antagonist Eric Gordon in the film Billy Madison, and Dean Armitage in the film Get Out.[citation needed]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5052448</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Mone Kamishiraishi</name>
        <birthday>1998-01-27</birthday>
        <age>19</age>
        <biography>Mone Kamishiraishi (上白石 萌音[2], Kamishiraishi Mone?, born 27 January 1998, in Kagoshima, Kagoshima Prefecture)[1] is a Japanese actress and singer.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5311514</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Justin Theroux</name>
        <birthday>1971-08-10</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Justin Paul Theroux (born August 10, 1971)[1] is an American actor and screenwriter. He is best known for his work with film director David Lynch. He appeared in Mulholland Drive (2001) and Inland Empire (2006). He is also known as a screenwriter for films such as Tropic Thunder, Iron Man 2, Rock of Ages, and Zoolander 2. Since 2014, he has starred in the HBO series The Leftovers and more recently starred in the 2016 film The Girl on the Train.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3631112</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Octavius J. Johnson</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2072233</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Octavia Spencer</name>
        <birthday>1972-05-25</birthday>
        <age>45</age>
        <biography>Octavia Lenora Spencer[1] (born May 25, 1972)[2][3] is an American actress and author. She made her film debut in A Time to Kill. Her breakthrough came in 2011, when she starred as Minny Jackson in the period film The Help, for which she won the Academy Award, Golden Globe, SAG, BAFTA, and Critics' Choice Movie Award for Best Supporting Actress. She had a critically acclaimed performance in Ryan Coogler's drama Fruitvale Station (2013), for which she received the National Board of Review Award for Best Supporting Actress. Recently, Spencer has received acclaim for her work in the films Get on Up, Black or White, Smashed, Snowpiercer, The Divergent Series: Insurgent, and Zootopia. In 2017, she received Academy Award, Golden Globe, and SAG nominations for Best Supporting Actress for her performance as mathematician Dorothy Vaughan in the drama Hidden Figures.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4846340</movie>
            <movie>tt4481414</movie>
            <movie>tt2872518</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sunny Pawar</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3741834</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Chris Hemsworth</name>
        <birthday>1983-08-11</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Chris Hemsworth (born 11 August 1983)[1][2] is an Australian actor. He is known for playing Kim Hyde in the Australian TV series Home and Away (2004) and Thor in the Marvel Cinematic Universe since 2011. Hemsworth has also appeared in the science fiction action film Star Trek (2009), the thriller adventure A Perfect Getaway (2009), the horror comedy The Cabin in the Woods (2012), the dark-fantasy action film Snow White and the Huntsman (2012), the war film Red Dawn (2012), and the biographical sports drama film Rush (2013).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3501632</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Charlize Theron</name>
        <birthday>1975-08-07</birthday>
        <age>42</age>
        <biography>Charlize Theron (/ʃɑːrˈliːz ˈθɛrən/ shar-LEEZ THERR-ən; Afrikaans: [ʃarˈlis trɔn];[2] born 7 August 1975)[3] is a South African and American actress and film producer. She has starred in several Hollywood films, such as The Devil's Advocate (1997), Mighty Joe Young (1998), The Cider House Rules (1999), Monster (2003), The Italian Job (2003), Hancock (2008), A Million Ways to Die in the West (2014), Mad Max: Fury Road (2015) and The Fate of the Furious (2017).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4630562</movie>
            <movie>tt2406566</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Carice van Houten</name>
        <birthday>1976-09-05</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Carice Anouk van Houten (Dutch pronunciation: [kaːˈris ɑˈnuk vɑn ˈɦʌu̯tə(n)];[3] born 5 September 1976) is a Dutch actress and singer. Born in Leiderdorp, a town in the western Netherlands, she was brought up by writer and theatre-radio producer Theodore van Houten. Her younger sister Jelka is also an actress. She was exposed to the performing arts at an early age and studied at the Maastricht Academy of Dramatic Arts and the Kleinkunstacademie Theaterschool in Amsterdam. Her first leading role as the eponymous protagonist in the television film Suzy Q (1999) won her the Golden Calf for Best Acting in a Television Drama; two years later, she won her second Golden Calf for Best Actress for Undercover Kitty (2001).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1895315</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dane DeHaan</name>
        <birthday>1986-02-06</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Dane William DeHaan (/dəˈhɑːn/ də-HAHN; born February 6, 1986[2][3][4]) is an American actor. He is known for playing Jesse on the HBO series In Treatment, and for his roles in the films Chronicle (2012), The Place Beyond the Pines (2013), Kill Your Darlings (2013), The Amazing Spider-Man 2 (2014), Life (2015) and A Cure for Wellness (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4731136</movie>
            <movie>tt2239822</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Demi Lovato</name>
        <birthday>1992-08-20</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Demetria Devonne "Demi" Lovato (/ˈdɛmi loʊˈvɑːtoʊ/ DEM-ee loh-VAH-toh or lə-VAH-toh; born August 20, 1992) is an American singer, songwriter, and actress. After making her debut as a child actress in Barney &amp; Friends, Lovato rose to prominence in 2008 when she starred in the Disney Channel television film Camp Rock and released her debut single This Is Me which peaked at number nine on the Billboard Hot 100. The success of the film and its soundtrack resulted in a recording contract with Hollywood Records. Her debut album, Don't Forget (2008), debuted at number two on the US Billboard 200. The following year, Lovato was cast as the titular character of the television series Sonny with a Chance and she released her sophomore album, Here We Go Again, which became her first one to top the Billboard 200 chart.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2398241</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dominic West</name>
        <birthday>1969-10-15</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Dominic Gerard Francis Eagleton West[2] (born 15 October 1969)[3] is an English actor, musician, and director. He is known for playing Jimmy McNulty in The Wire, and won the British Academy Television Award for Best Actor at the 2012 British Academy Television Awards for portraying serial killer Fred West in Appropriate Adult.[4] He stars as Noah Solloway on the Showtime drama series, The Affair, for which he has received a Golden Globe nomination.[5]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1365519</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ethan Hawke</name>
        <birthday>1970-11-06</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Ethan Green Hawke (born November 6, 1970)[1] is an American actor, writer, and director. He has been nominated for four Academy Awards and a Tony Award. Hawke has directed two feature films, three Off-Broadway plays, and a documentary, and written the novels The Hottest State (1996), Ash Wednesday (2002), and Rules for a Knight (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3721954</movie>
            <movie>tt2239822</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Cressida Bonas</name>
        <birthday>1989-02-18</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Cressida Curzon Bonas (born 18 February 1989)[2] is an English actress, dancer and model. She is the youngest daughter of Lady Mary-Gaye Curzon and entrepreneur Jeffrey Bonas, and a granddaughter of Edward Curzon, 6th Earl Howe.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4030600</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rosa Salazar</name>
        <birthday>1985-07-16</birthday>
        <age>32</age>
        <biography>Rosa Bianca Salazar (born July 16, 1985) is an American actress. She was raised in Greenbelt, Maryland. She began performing in New York City and moved to Los Angeles, California in 2009 to pursue acting. She appeared in several CollegeHumor sketches. She is best known for her roles as Zoe DeHaven on the NBC series Parenthood, and Nurse Maria in the FX anthology series American Horror Story: Murder House. She appeared in the 2015 films The Divergent Series: Insurgent, as Lynn, and Maze Runner: The Scorch Trials, as Brenda.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0437086</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Barry Pepper</name>
        <birthday>1970-04-04</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Barry Robert Pepper (born April 4, 1970) is a Canadian actor. He is best known for roles such as Private Daniel Jackson in Saving Private Ryan (1998), Dean Stanton in The Green Mile (1999), Jonnie Goodboy Tyler in Battlefield Earth (2000), Roger Maris in 61* (2001), Sergeant Michael Strank in Flags of Our Fathers (2006) and "Lucky" Ned Pepper in True Grit (2010). He has been nominated for three Screen Actors Guild Awards and a Golden Globe Award. For his role as Robert F. Kennedy in the miniseries The Kennedys (2011), Pepper won the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Lead Actor in a Miniseries or Movie.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3095734</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Chris Pratt</name>
        <birthday>1979-06-21</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Christopher Michael "Chris" Pratt (born June 21, 1979) is an American actor. Pratt came to prominence from his television roles, including Bright Abbott in The WB drama series Everwood and Andy Dwyer in the NBC sitcom Parks and Recreation. His early film career began with supporting roles in such mainstream films as Wanted, Jennifer's Body, Moneyball, The Five-Year Engagement, Zero Dark Thirty, Delivery Man and Her.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1355644</movie>
            <movie>tt3896198</movie>
            <movie>tt4881806</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Luke Evans</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2771200</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Nicholas Hamilton</name>
        <birthday>1992-03-28</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Nicolas "Nic" Hamilton (born 28 March 1992) is a British racing driver from England who currently competes in the British Touring Car Championship. He races with a specially-modified car due to his cerebral palsy.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1396484</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Zoey Deutch</name>
        <birthday>1994-11-10</birthday>
        <age>23</age>
        <biography>Zoey Francis Thompson Deutch (born November 10, 1994)[1][2] is an American actress. She is known for portraying Rose Hathaway in Vampire Academy (2014), Beverly in the Richard Linklater film Everybody Wants Some!! (2016), Stephanie Fleming in Why Him? (2016), and Samantha Kingston in Before I Fall (2017). Her other film roles include Beautiful Creatures (2013) and Dirty Grandpa (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4501244</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Trey Tucker</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3922818</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Al Pacino</name>
        <birthday>1940-04-25</birthday>
        <age>77</age>
        <biography>Alfredo James "Al" Pacino (/pəˈtʃiːnoʊ/; born April 25, 1940) is an American actor of stage and screen, filmmaker, and screenwriter. Pacino has had a career spanning more than fifty years, during which time he has received numerous accolades and honors both competitive and honorary, among them an Academy Award, two Tony Awards, two Primetime Emmy Awards, a British Academy Film Award, four Golden Globe Awards, the Lifetime Achievement Award from the American Film Institute, the Golden Globe Cecil B. DeMille Award, and the National Medal of Arts. He is also one of few performers to have won a competitive Oscar, an Emmy and a Tony Award for acting, dubbed the "Triple Crown of Acting".</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1302006</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jane Levy</name>
        <birthday>1989-12-29</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Jane Colburn Levy (born December 29, 1989)[1] is an American actress. In early 2011, she made her television debut in the Showtime drama series Shameless playing Mandy Milkovich, and later began starring as Tessa Altman, a leading character on the ABC comedy series Suburgatory (2011-14).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3095734</movie>
            <movie>tt4160708</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Robin Wright</name>
        <birthday>1966-04-08</birthday>
        <age>51</age>
        <biography>Robin Gayle Wright[1] (born April 8, 1966) is an American actress and director. She stars as Claire Underwood in the Netflix political drama web television series House of Cards, for which she won the Golden Globe Award for Best Actress – Television Series Drama in 2013, making her the first actress to win a Golden Globe for a web television series. Wright received Primetime Emmy nominations for House of Cards in 2013, 2014, 2015 and 2016.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0451279</movie>
            <movie>tt1856101</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Boyd Holbrook</name>
        <birthday>1981-09-01</birthday>
        <age>36</age>
        <biography>Robert Boyd Holbrook[2] (born September 1, 1981)[2] is an American actor and fashion model. He has appeared in films such as Milk, Out of the Furnace, Run All Night, A Walk Among the Tombstones, and Gone Girl, Logan and stars as DEA Agent Steve Murphy in the Netflix series Narcos. In 2017, he portrayed villain Donald Pierce in Logan.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3315342</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Scott Eastwood</name>
        <birthday>1986-03-21</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Scott Eastwood (born Scott Clinton Reeves; March 21, 1986)[3] is an American actor, model, and professional skydiver. He has appeared in the films Flags of Our Fathers (2006), Gran Torino (2008), Invictus (2009), The Forger (2012), Trouble with the Curve (2012), Texas Chainsaw (2013), Fury (2014), The Perfect Wave (2014), The Longest Ride (2015), and Suicide Squad (2016). He has also been the model for the fragrance Cool Water by Davidoff. He is the youngest son of Academy Award-winning actor-director Clint Eastwood and second youngest of Jacelyn Reeves.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4630562</movie>
            <movie>tt2557478</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ben O'Brien</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4034228</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Emily Mortimer</name>
        <birthday>1971-12-01</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Emily Kathleen Anne Mortimer[1] (born 1 December 1971) is an English actress and screenwriter. She began acting in stage productions, and has since appeared in several film and television roles. In 2003, she won an Independent Spirit Award for her performance in Lovely and Amazing. She is also known for playing roles in Match Point (2005), Lars and the Real Girl (2007), Chaos Theory (2008), Harry Brown (2009), Shutter Island (2010), Hugo (2011), and the HBO series The Newsroom.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5028340</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>James Cromwell</name>
        <birthday>1940-01-27</birthday>
        <age>77</age>
        <biography>James Oliver Cromwell (born January 27, 1940) is an American actor and producer. Some of his more notable films include Star Trek: First Contact (1996), L.A. Confidential (1997), The Green Mile (1999), Space Cowboys (2000), The Sum of All Fears (2002), I, Robot (2004), The Longest Yard (2005), The Queen (2006) and The Artist (2011), as well as the television series Six Feet Under (2003–2005), 24 (2007) and Halt and Catch Fire (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4776998</movie>
            <movie>tt4881806</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sarah Silverman</name>
        <birthday>1970-12-01</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Sarah Kate Silverman (born December 1, 1970)[1] is an American stand-up comedian, actress, producer, and writer. Her comedy addresses social taboos and controversial topics, such as racism, sexism, and religion, having her comic character endorse them in a sarcastic fashion.[2][3] For her work on television, she won two Primetime Emmy Awards.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5848272</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ludi Lin</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3717490</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Alicia Vikander</name>
        <birthday>1988-10-03</birthday>
        <age>29</age>
        <biography>Alicia Amanda Vikander (Swedish pronunciation: [aˈliːsɪa vɪˈkandɛr]; born 3 October 1988) is a Swedish actress and former dancer. Born and raised in Gothenburg, she began acting as a child in minor stage productions at The Göteborg Opera and trained as a ballet dancer at the Royal Swedish Ballet School in Stockholm and the School of American Ballet in New York. She began her professional acting career by appearing in Swedish short films and television series and first gained recognition in Northern Europe for her role as Josefin Björn-Tegebrandt in the TV drama Andra Avenyn (2008–10).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1365519</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Marion Cotillard</name>
        <birthday>1975-09-30</birthday>
        <age>42</age>
        <biography>Marion Cotillard (French pronunciation: [ma.ʁjɔ̃ kɔ.ti.jaʁ] ( listen); born 30 September 1975)[1] is a French actress, singer-songwriter, musician, environmentalist and spokesperson for Greenpeace[2] who achieved international fame with the film La Vie en Rose (2007). She is the recipient of an Academy Award, a BAFTA Award, a Golden Globe Award, two César Awards, a European Award, and a Lumières Award. Cotillard has appeared in more than 50 feature films and is also known for being the face of Lady Dior handbags since 2008. She became a Knight of the Order of Arts and Letters in France in 2010 and promoted to Officer in 2016. Was named "The Most Bankable French Actress of the 21st Century" in 2014,[3] and described as "the great silent film actress of our time" by The Daily Telegraph's Robbie Collin, for her ability to show emotions only with her eyes and facial expressions, although she has never appeared in a silent film.[4] She received France's highest honor and was made a Knight of the Legion of Honour in 2016.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2094766</movie>
            <movie>tt3640424</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Alison Sudol</name>
        <birthday>1984-12-23</birthday>
        <age>33</age>
        <biography>Alison Loren Sudol (born December 23, 1984) is an American actress, singer, songwriter and writer.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4123430</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ruby Rose</name>
        <birthday>1986-03-20</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Ruby Rose Langenheim (born 20 March 1986), better known as Ruby Rose, is an Australian model, DJ, recording artist, actress, television presenter, and former MTV VJ. Rose emerged in the media spotlight as a presenter on MTV Australia, followed by several high-profile modelling gigs, notably as the face of Maybelline New York in Australia. In addition to her modelling career, she has co-hosted various television shows, namely Australia's Next Top Model and The Project on Network Ten.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4425200</movie>
            <movie>tt4779682</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Forest Whitaker</name>
        <birthday>1961-07-15</birthday>
        <age>56</age>
        <biography>Forest Steven Whitaker III (born July 15, 1961) is an American actor, producer, and director.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2543164</movie>
            <movie>tt1825683</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>RJ Cyler</name>
        <birthday>1995-03-21</birthday>
        <age>22</age>
        <biography>Ronald "RJ" Cyler II (born March 21, 1995) is an American actor. He is best known for his roles in Me and Earl and the Dying Girl and Power Rangers.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3717490</movie>
            <movie>tt4537896</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Fassbender</name>
        <birthday>1977-04-02</birthday>
        <age>40</age>
        <biography>Michael Fassbender (born 2 April 1977) is a German-born Irish actor. His feature film debut was in the fantasy war epic 300 (2007) as a Spartan warrior; his earlier roles included various stage productions, as well as starring roles on television such as in the HBO miniseries Band of Brothers (2001) and the Sky One fantasy drama Hex (2004–05). He first came to prominence for his role as IRA activist Bobby Sands in Hunger (2008), for which he won a British Independent Film Award. Subsequent roles include in the independent film Fish Tank (2009), as a Royal Marines lieutenant in Inglourious Basterds (2009), as Edward Rochester in the 2011 film adaptation of Jane Eyre, as Carl Jung in A Dangerous Method (2011), as a sentient android in Prometheus (2012), and in the musical comedy-drama Frank (2014) as an eccentric musician loosely inspired by Frank Sidebottom.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2094766</movie>
            <movie>tt3385516</movie>
            <movie>tt2316204</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Daniel Wu</name>
        <birthday>1974-09-30</birthday>
        <age>43</age>
        <biography>Daniel Wu Yin-cho (simplified Chinese: 吴彦祖; traditional Chinese: 吳彥祖; pinyin: Wú Yànzǔ; jyutping: ng4 jin6zou2; born September 30, 1974) is an American actor, director and producer based in Hong Kong, and as of 2015, starring as Sunny in the AMC martial arts drama series Into the Badlands. Since his film debut in 1998, he has been featured in over 60 films. Wu has been called "the young Donnie Yen,"[1] and is known as a "flexible and distinctive" leading actor in the Chinese-language film industry.[2][3]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1365519</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sally Hawkins</name>
        <birthday>1976-04-27</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Sally Cecilia Hawkins (born 27 April 1976) is an English actress. She made her film debut in Mike Leigh's All or Nothing in 2002. She continued working with Leigh, appearing in Vera Drake (2004) and in Happy-Go-Lucky (2008), for which she won several awards including the Golden Globe Award for Best Actress in a Musical or Comedy, and the Silver Bear for Best Actress at the Berlin Film Festival.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3721954</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Eddie Redmayne</name>
        <birthday>1982-01-06</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Edward John David Redmayne, OBE (/ˈrɛdˌmeɪn/; born 6 January 1982) is an English actor of stage and screen. Born and raised in Westminster, he studied history of art at Trinity College, Cambridge, after which he briefly dabbled with a modelling career. Redmayne began his professional acting career as a youth in West End theatre before making his screen debut in 1998 with guest appearances on television. His first film roles came in 2006 with Like Minds and The Good Shepherd, and he went on to play supporting roles in several films, including Savage Grace (2007), Elizabeth: The Golden Age (2007), and The Other Boleyn Girl (2008).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3183660</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ed Skrein</name>
        <birthday>1983-03-29</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Edward George "Ed" Skrein (born 29 March 1983) is an English actor and rapper. Outside of his rap career, he is best known for his roles as Daario Naharis in Season 3 of Game of Thrones, Frank Martin Jr. in The Transporter Refueled and Francis Freeman / Ajax in Deadpool (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1431045</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kari Matchett</name>
        <birthday>1970-03-25</birthday>
        <age>47</age>
        <biography>Kari Matchett (born March 25, 1970) is a Canadian actress.[1] She has appeared in films such as Apartment Hunting (2000), Angel Eyes (2001), Men with Brooms (2002), Cypher (2002), Civic Duty (2006), The Tree of Life (2011), and Maudie (2016). She is perhaps best known for her roles as Joan Campbell on Covert Affairs and as Kate Filmore in the cult favorite science fiction movie Cube 2: Hypercube.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3721954</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Brianna Hildebrand</name>
        <birthday>1996-08-14</birthday>
        <age>21</age>
        <biography>Brianna Caitlin Hildebrand (born August 14, 1996) is an American actress. She is known for appearing in the web series Annie Undocumented, and as Negasonic Teenage Warhead in the 2016 film Deadpool.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5463162</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jason Isaacs</name>
        <birthday>1963-06-06</birthday>
        <age>54</age>
        <biography>Jason Isaacs (born 6 June 1963) is an English actor.[2] He is known for playing Lucius Malfoy in the Harry Potter films, Colonel William Tavington in The Patriot, and criminal Michael Caffee in the American television series Brotherhood.[3] In December 2016, he played the lead antagonist in the Netflix supernatural hit series The OA.[4]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4731136</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Katherine McNamara</name>
        <birthday>1995-11-22</birthday>
        <age>22</age>
        <biography>Katherine Grace McNamara[1] (born November 22, 1995[1][2]) is an American actress. She is known for her role as Harper Munroe on the MTV comedy series Happyland, and for her lead role as Clary Fray on the Freeform fantasy series Shadowhunters.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4500922</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Rachel McAdams</name>
        <birthday>1978-11-17</birthday>
        <age>39</age>
        <biography>Rachel Anne McAdams (born November 17, 1978) is a Canadian actress. After graduating from a four-year theatre program at York University in 2001, she initially worked in Canadian television and film productions such as the drama film Perfect Pie (2002) (for which she received a Genie Award nomination), the comedy film My Name Is Tanino (2002), and the comedy series Slings and Arrows (for which she won a Gemini Award). In 2002, she made her Hollywood film debut in the comedy The Hot Chick. McAdams rose to fame in 2004 with her roles in the comedy Mean Girls and the romantic drama The Notebook. In 2005, she starred in the romantic comedy Wedding Crashers, the psychological thriller Red Eye, and the family comedy-drama The Family Stone. She was hailed by the media as Hollywood's new "it girl",[1][2] and received a BAFTA nomination for Best Rising Star.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1211837</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Mark Rylance</name>
        <birthday>1960-01-18</birthday>
        <age>57</age>
        <biography>Sir David Mark Rylance Waters (born 18 January 1960) is an English actor, theatre director and playwright. He was the first artistic director of Shakespeare's Globe in London, from 1995 to 2005. His film appearances include Prospero's Books (1991), Angels and Insects (1995), Institute Benjamenta (1996), and Intimacy (2001). Rylance won the Academy Award and the BAFTA Award for Best Supporting Actor for his portrayal of Rudolf Abel in Bridge of Spies (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5013056</movie>
            <movie>tt1677720</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Zazie Beetz</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5463162</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Andy Serkis</name>
        <birthday>1964-04-20</birthday>
        <age>53</age>
        <biography>Andrew Clement "Andy" Serkis[1][2] (born 20 April 1964) is an English film actor, director and author. He is best known for his performance capture roles comprising motion capture acting, animation and voice work for such computer-generated characters as Gollum in The Lord of the Rings film trilogy (2001–2003) and The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey (2012), King Kong in the eponymous 2005 film, Caesar in the Planet of the Apes reboot series (2011–present), Captain Haddock / Sir Francis Haddock in Steven Spielberg's The Adventures of Tintin (2011) and Supreme Leader Snoke in Star Wars: The Force Awakens (2015). Upcoming performance capture roles include Caesar in War for the Planet of the Apes (2017), Supreme Leader Snoke in Star Wars: The Last Jedi (2017), and Baloo in Jungle Book (2018).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3450958</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>John C. Reilly</name>
        <birthday>1965-05-24</birthday>
        <age>52</age>
        <biography>John Christopher Reilly (born May 24, 1965)[1][2] is an American actor, comedian, singer, screenwriter, and producer.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3731562</movie>
            <movie>tt5848272</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dwayne Johnson</name>
        <birthday>1972-05-02</birthday>
        <age>45</age>
        <biography>Dwayne Douglas Johnson (born May 2, 1972), also known by his ring name The Rock, is an American actor, producer, singer, and professional wrestler. He holds American and Canadian citizenships.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3521164</movie>
            <movie>tt4630562</movie>
            <movie>tt1469304</movie>
            <movie>tt2283362</movie>
            <movie>tt2231461</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Linda Cardellini</name>
        <birthday>1975-06-25</birthday>
        <age>42</age>
        <biography>Linda Edna Cardellini (born June 25, 1975) is an American actress and voice actress.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4276820</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Paul Rudd</name>
        <birthday>1969-04-06</birthday>
        <age>48</age>
        <biography>Paul Stephen Rudd (born April 6, 1969) is an American actor, comedian, writer, and producer. He studied theatre at the University of Kansas and the British American Drama Academy, before making his acting debut in 1992 with NBC's drama series Sisters. He is known for his starring roles in the film The Cider House Rules (1999) and the comedy films Clueless (1995), Halloween: The Curse of Michael Myers (1995), Wet Hot American Summer (2001), Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy (2004), The 40-Year-Old Virgin (2005), Knocked Up (2007), Role Models (2008), I Love You, Man (2009), Dinner for Schmucks (2010), Our Idiot Brother (2011), Wanderlust (2012), This Is 40 (2012), and Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues (2013), and for playing the superhero Scott Lang / Ant-Man in Marvel Studios' Ant-Man (2015) and Captain America: Civil War (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5095030</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>T.J. Miller</name>
        <birthday>1981-06-04</birthday>
        <age>36</age>
        <biography>Todd Joseph "T. J." Miller (born June 4, 1981) is an American actor, stand-up comedian, producer and writer. He currently stars as Erlich Bachman in the HBO sitcom Silicon Valley. Miller has also performed in such films as Cloverfield (2008), She's Out of My League (2010), Yogi Bear (2010), How to Train Your Dragon (2010), How to Train Your Dragon 2 (2014), Transformers: Age of Extinction (2014), Big Hero 6 (2014), and Deadpool (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1711525</movie>
            <movie>tt5463162</movie>
            <movie>tt1677720</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Miles Christopher Bakshi</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3874544</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Adria Arjona</name>
        <birthday>1992-04-25</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Adria Arjona Torres (born April 25, 1992) is an American actress. She is best known for her role as Emily in the HBO television series True Detective (2015) and as Dani Silva in the CBS television series Person of Interest (2014–2015). She currently stars in the NBC television series Emerald City as Dorothy Gale.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2557478</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Lucas Till</name>
        <birthday>1990-08-10</birthday>
        <age>27</age>
        <biography>Lucas Daniel Till (born August 10, 1990) is an American film and television actor. He began acting in the early 2000s and has appeared in a number of film and television productions including roles on House, Stoker and Hannah Montana: The Movie. He is known for his role as Havok in the X-Men (film series) starting with 2011 X-Men: First Class and plays Angus MacGyver in the television reboot of MacGyver, which premiered in September 2016.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3095734</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Alden Ehrenreich</name>
        <birthday>1989-11-22</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Alden Caleb Ehrenreich (US pronunciation: /ˈɛrənraɪk/; born November 22, 1989) is an American actor.[1][2] He made his feature film debut in Francis Ford Coppola's independent film Tetro (2009) and appeared in Coppola's subsequent film Twixt (2011). In 2013, he appeared in Woody Allen's Blue Jasmine, Park Chan-wook's Stoker and starred in Richard LaGravenese's Beautiful Creatures. In 2016, he starred as Hobie Doyle in the Coen brothers comedy Hail, Caesar! and as Frank Forbes in Warren Beatty's Rules Don't Apply. In 2018, he will star as Han Solo in an as of yet untitled Star Wars spin-off film revolving around the character's younger years.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3778644</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Auli'i Cravalho</name>
        <birthday>2000-11-22</birthday>
        <age>17</age>
        <biography>Auli'i Cravalho (/aʊˈliː.i krəˈvæljoʊ/ ow-LEE-ee krə-VAL-yoh;[2][3] born November 22, 2000)[1] is an American actress and singer. She made her acting debut as the title character in the 2016 film Moana.[4][5][6][7]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3521164</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Aiden Haggarty</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2763304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Theo James</name>
        <birthday>1984-12-16</birthday>
        <age>33</age>
        <biography>Theodore Peter James Kinnaird Taptiklis[1] (born 16 December 1984), better known as Theo James, is an English actor known for his roles as Jed Harper in Bedlam (2011), Walter William Clark, Jr. in the crime drama Golden Boy (2013), Tobias "Four" Eaton in the film adaptations of The Divergent Series, and David in Underworld: Awakening (2012) and Underworld: Blood Wars (2016).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3717252</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Lucien Laviscount</name>
        <birthday>1992-06-09</birthday>
        <age>25</age>
        <biography>Lucien Leon Laviscount (born 9 June 1992) is a British actor and recording artist best known for his portrayal of Jonah Kirby on popular BBC One drama Waterloo Road.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4030600</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jaime FitzSimons</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1386697</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Katherine Waterston</name>
        <birthday>1980-03-03</birthday>
        <age>37</age>
        <biography>Katherine Boyer Waterston (born March 3, 1980)[1] is an American actress. She made her feature film debut in Michael Clayton (2007). She then had supporting roles in films including Robot &amp; Frank, Being Flynn (both 2012) and The Disappearance of Eleanor Rigby: Her (2013) before her leading role as Shasta Fay Hepworth in Paul Thomas Anderson's Inherent Vice (2014). In 2015, she portrayed Chrisann Brennan in Steve Jobs. She had a starring role in the Harry Potter prequel, Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them (2016). In 2017, Waterston will star in Alien: Covenant, a prequel to Ridley Scott's Alien film series.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2316204</movie>
            <movie>tt4123430</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Abhishek Bharate</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3741834</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Sissy Spacek</name>
        <birthday>1949-12-25</birthday>
        <age>68</age>
        <biography>Mary Elizabeth "Sissy" Spacek (/ˈspeɪsɛk/; born December 25, 1949) is an American actress and singer. She began her career in the early 1970s and first gained attention for her role in the film Badlands (1973). Her career-defining role came in 1976 when she played the title character of Carrie White in Brian De Palma's horror film Carrie, based on the first novel by Stephen King, for which she earned an Oscar nomination (very rare for an actor or actress in a horror movie). She won the Academy Award for Best Actress for her portrayal of Loretta Lynn in the 1980 film Coal Miner's Daughter, and also earned a Grammy nomination for the song "Coal Miner's Daughter" from the film's soundtrack. She went on to receive further Oscar nominations for her roles in Missing (1982), The River (1984) and Crimes of the Heart (1986). Coal Miner's Daughter and Crimes of the Heart also won her the Golden Globe Award for Best Actress in a Musical or Comedy.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2837574</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Christoph Waltz</name>
        <birthday>1956-10-04</birthday>
        <age>61</age>
        <biography>Christoph Waltz (German pronun­cia­tion: [ˈkrɪstɔf ˈvalts]; born 4 October 1956) is an Austrian-German actor.[1][2][3] Widely known for his works with American filmmaker Quentin Tarantino, he received acclaim for portraying SS-Standartenführer Hans Landa in Inglourious Basterds (2009) and bounty hunter Dr. King Schultz in Django Unchained (2012). For each of those performances, he won an Academy Award, a BAFTA Award, and a Golden Globe Award for Best Supporting Actor. He also received the Best Actor Award at the Cannes Film Festival and a Screen Actors Guild Award for his portrayal of Landa.[4]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt0437086</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Seth MacFarlane</name>
        <birthday>1973-10-26</birthday>
        <age>44</age>
        <biography>Seth Woodbury MacFarlane (/ˈsɛθ ˈwʊdbɛri məkˈfɑːrlɪn/; born October 26, 1973)[1] is an American television producer, filmmaker, actor, and singer, working primarily in animation and comedy, as well as live-action and other genres. MacFarlane is the creator of the TV series Family Guy (1999–2003, 2005–present), co-creator of the TV series American Dad! (2005–present) and The Cleveland Show (2009–13). He also wrote, directed, and starred in the films Ted (2012), its sequel Ted 2 (2015), and A Million Ways to Die in the West (2014).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3470600</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Gina Piersanti</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4814760</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Aaron Taylor-Johnson</name>
        <birthday>1990-06-13</birthday>
        <age>27</age>
        <biography>Aaron Taylor-Johnson (born Aaron Perry Johnson;[1] 13 June 1990)[2][3] is an English actor, best known as the title character in the Kick-Ass films and Quicksilver in Avengers: Age of Ultron (2015).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4550098</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Richard Donelly</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4034228</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Marisa Tomei</name>
        <birthday>1964-12-04</birthday>
        <age>53</age>
        <biography>Marisa Tomei (/məˈrɪsə toʊˈmeɪ/; Italian pronunciation: [maˈriːza toˈmɛi]; born December 4, 1964)[1] is an American actress. In a career spanning three decades, Tomei had initial success in films as a young actress, followed by a series of unsuccessful films, then a resurgence with a series of critically acclaimed films. Following her work on the television series As the World Turns, she came to prominence as a cast member on The Cosby Show spin-off A Different World in 1987.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2250912</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dan Stevens</name>
        <birthday>1982-10-10</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Daniel Jonathan "Dan" Stevens[1] (born 10 October 1982)[2] is an English actor. He is best known for his roles as Matthew Crawley in the ITV period drama series Downton Abbey, as "David" in the thriller film The Guest, Sir Lancelot in Night at the Museum: Secret of the Tomb, and as The Beast/Prince in Walt Disney's live-action adaptation of Beauty and the Beast. He currently stars as David Haller in FX series Legion.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4680182</movie>
            <movie>tt2771200</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jeremy Renner</name>
        <birthday>1971-01-07</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Jeremy Lee Renner (born January 7, 1971)[1][2][3] is an American actor and singer. Throughout the 2000s, Renner appeared largely in independent films such as Dahmer (2002) and Neo Ned (2005). He also appeared in supporting roles in bigger films such as S.W.A.T. (2003) and 28 Weeks Later (2007). He then turned in a much-praised performance in The Town (2010), for which he received an Academy Award nomination for Best Supporting Actor.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2543164</movie>
            <movie>tt5095030</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Eloise Mumford</name>
        <birthday>1986-09-24</birthday>
        <age>31</age>
        <biography>Eloise Mumford (born September 24, 1986)[1] is an American actress known for her roles on the television series Lone Star, The River and the Fifty Shades of Grey films.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4465564</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jonah Hill</name>
        <birthday>1983-12-20</birthday>
        <age>34</age>
        <biography>Jonah Hill Feldstein (born December 20, 1983), better known as Jonah Hill, is an American actor, producer, screenwriter and comedian. Hill is known for his comedic roles in films such as Accepted (2006), Grandma's Boy (2006), Superbad (2007), Knocked Up (2007), Forgetting Sarah Marshal (2008), Get Him to the Greek (2010), 21 Jump Street (2012), This Is the End (2013), 22 Jump Street (2014) and War Dogs (2016), as well as his performances in Moneyball (2011) and The Wolf of Wall Street (2013), for which he received Academy Award nominations for Best Supporting Actor.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt6288124</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Scott Goldman</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3183660</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Dacre Montgomery</name>
        <birthday>1994-11-22</birthday>
        <age>23</age>
        <biography>Dacre Montgomery (born 22 November 1994) is an Australian actor. He is best known for his role as Jason the Red Ranger in the 2017 reboot of Power Rangers.[1] He will appear in the second season of Stranger Things in late October 2017.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3717490</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>John Carroll Lynch</name>
        <birthday>1963-08-01</birthday>
        <age>54</age>
        <biography>John Carroll Lynch (born August 1, 1963)[1][2] is an American actor and director. He first gained notice for his role as Norm Gunderson in Fargo. He is also known for his television work on the ABC sitcom The Drew Carey Show as the title character's cross-dressing brother, Steve Carey, as well as on American Horror Story: Freak Show as Twisty the Clown. His films include Face/Off, Gran Torino, Shutter Island, Ted 2, The Invitation, and Zodiac. Most recently, he portrayed McDonald's co-founder Maurice "Mac" McDonald in The Founder.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4276820</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Mia Goth</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4731136</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Johnny Depp</name>
        <birthday>1963-06-09</birthday>
        <age>54</age>
        <biography>John Christopher "Johnny" Depp II (born June 9, 1963)[2] is an American actor, producer, and musician. He has won the Golden Globe Award and Screen Actors Guild Award for Best Actor. He rose to prominence on the 1980s television series 21 Jump Street, becoming a teen idol.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1790809</movie>
            <movie>tt4123430</movie>
            <movie>tt2296777</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kevin Hart</name>
        <birthday>1979-07-06</birthday>
        <age>38</age>
        <biography>Kevin Darnell Hart[1] (born July 6, 1979)[2] is an American actor, comedian, writer, and producer. Born and raised in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Hart began his career by winning several amateur comedy competitions at clubs throughout New England, culminating in his first real break in 2000 when he was cast by Judd Apatow for a recurring role on the TV series Undeclared. The series lasted only one season, but he soon landed other roles in movies like Paper Soldiers (2002), Scary Movie 3 (2003), Soul Plane (2004), In the Mix (2005) and Little Fockers (2010).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2283362</movie>
            <movie>tt1987680</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Anthony Hopkins</name>
        <birthday>1937-12-31</birthday>
        <age>80</age>
        <biography>Sir Philip Anthony Hopkins CBE (born 31 December 1937), is a Welsh actor of film, stage, and television.[1] After graduating from the Royal Welsh College of Music &amp; Drama in 1957, he trained at the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art in London, and was then spotted by Laurence Olivier who invited him to join the Royal National Theatre. In 1968, he got his break in film in The Lion in Winter, playing Richard the Lionheart.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3371366</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Richard Pyros</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2119532</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Robert Redford</name>
        <birthday>1936-08-18</birthday>
        <age>81</age>
        <biography>Charles Robert Redford Jr. (born August 18, 1936)[3][4] is an American actor, director, producer, businessman, environmentalist, and philanthropist. Redford is the founder of the Sundance Film Festival.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5155780</movie>
            <movie>tt2837574</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Gemma Chan</name>
        <birthday>1982-11-29</birthday>
        <age>35</age>
        <biography>Gemma Chan (born 29 November 1982)[1] is a British film, television, and theatre actress and former fashion model. She portrays Charlotte in season four of the Showtime and ITV2 series Secret Diary of a Call Girl; Ruth in Channel 4's Fresh Meat; Mia Bennett in the BBC's Doctor Who "The Waters of Mars" and Soo Lin in Sherlock. She also appeared in Exam and Paramount Pictures' action-thriller Jack Ryan: Shadow Recruit. She stars in Humans, an AMC/Channel 4 science-fiction drama, which premiered in June 2015.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3371366</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kate Winslet</name>
        <birthday>1975-10-05</birthday>
        <age>42</age>
        <biography>Kate Elizabeth Winslet, CBE (born 5 October 1975), is an English actress and singer.[1]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4682786</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Daniel Kaluuya</name>
        <birthday>1989-05-08</birthday>
        <age>28</age>
        <biography>Daniel Kaluuya (born 8 May 1989) is an English actor and writer. Kaluuya is known for starring as Chris Washington in the 2017 horror film Get Out,[1] Posh Kenneth in the E4 teen-drama Skins, and Bing in the Black Mirror episode "Fifteen Million Merits".</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt5052448</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Morgan Freeman</name>
        <birthday>1937-06-01</birthday>
        <age>80</age>
        <biography>Morgan Freeman[2] (born June 1, 1937)[3] is an American actor, producer and narrator. Freeman won an Academy Award in 2005 for Best Supporting Actor with Million Dollar Baby (2004), and he has received Oscar nominations for his performances in Street Smart (1987), Driving Miss Daisy (1989), The Shawshank Redemption (1994) and Invictus (2009). He has also won a Golden Globe Award and a Screen Actors Guild Award.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2568862</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Kelly Rohrbach</name>
        <birthday>1990-01-21</birthday>
        <age>27</age>
        <biography>Kelly Wholey Rohrbach (born January 21, 1990) is an American model and actress.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1469304</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Cheryl Ladd</name>
        <birthday>1951-07-12</birthday>
        <age>66</age>
        <biography>Cheryl Ladd (born Cheryl Jean Stoppelmoor; July 12, 1951) is an American actress, singer, and author. Ladd is best known for her role as Kris Munroe in the ABC television series Charlie's Angels, hired amid a swirl of publicity prior to its second season in 1977 to replace the departing Farrah Fawcett-Majors who played Jill Munroe, the sister of Ladd's character. Ladd remained with the show until its cancellation in 1981.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3462710</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Jeff Bridges</name>
        <birthday>1949-12-04</birthday>
        <age>68</age>
        <biography>Jeffrey Leon "Jeff" Bridges (born December 4, 1949) is an American actor, singer, and producer. He comes from a prominent acting family and appeared on the television series Sea Hunt (1958–60), with his father, Lloyd Bridges and brother, Beau Bridges. He won the Academy Award for Best Actor for his role as Otis "Bad" Blake in the 2009 film Crazy Heart, and earned Academy Award nominations for his roles in The Last Picture Show (1971), Thunderbolt and Lightfoot (1974), Starman (1984), The Contender (2000), True Grit (2010), and Hell or High Water (2016). His other films include Tron (1982), Jagged Edge (1985), The Fabulous Baker Boys (1989), The Fisher King (1991), Fearless (1993), The Big Lebowski (1998), Seabiscuit (2003), Iron Man (2008), Tron: Legacy (2010), and The Giver (2014).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4649466</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Martin Freeman</name>
        <birthday>1971-09-08</birthday>
        <age>46</age>
        <biography>Martin John Christopher Freeman[2] (born 8 September 1971)[3] is an English actor, who became known for portraying Tim Canterbury in the original UK version of sitcom mockumentary The Office, Dr. John Watson in the British crime drama Sherlock, Bilbo Baggins in Peter Jackson's The Hobbit film trilogy, and Lester Nygaard in the dark comedy-crime drama TV series Fargo.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1825683</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Clint Dyer</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt3707104</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ella Rumpf</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4954522</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Julianna Margulies</name>
        <birthday>1966-06-08</birthday>
        <age>51</age>
        <biography>Julianna Margulies (/dʒuːliˈɑːnə mɑːrɡəˈliːs/; ('Mar-ga-lease') born June 8, 1966) is an American actress and producer. After several small television roles, Margulies achieved both critical and commercial success in her role as Carol Hathaway on NBC's long-running medical drama ER, for which she won an Emmy Award. She also voiced Neera in Dinosaur (2000) and appeared in the miniseries The Mists of Avalon (2001). In 2009, she took on the lead role of Alicia Florrick in the American legal drama The Good Wife on CBS. Her performance has garnered acclaim: she won the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Lead Actress in a Drama Series twice, a Golden Globe, and a Television Critics Association Award.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1987680</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Andy Lau</name>
        <birthday>1961-09-27</birthday>
        <age>56</age>
        <biography>Andy Lau Tak-wah, BBS, MH, JP[4] (born 27 September 1961) is a Hong Kong actor, singer and film producer. He has been one of Hong Kong's most commercially successful film actors since the mid-1980s, performing in more than 160 films while maintaining a successful singing career at the same time.[5] In the 1990s, Lau was branded by the media as one of the Four Heavenly Kings of Cantopop.[6]</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2034800</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Javier Botet</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1396484</movie>
            <movie>tt5140878</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Josh Gad</name>
        <birthday>1981-02-23</birthday>
        <age>36</age>
        <biography>Joshua Ilan "Josh" Gad[1] (born February 23, 1981[2]) is an American actor, comedian and singer who is best known for voicing Olaf in Frozen, and for originating the role of Elder Arnold Cunningham in the Broadway musical The Book of Mormon.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2771200</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Gabrielle Union</name>
        <birthday>1972-10-29</birthday>
        <age>45</age>
        <biography>Gabrielle Monique Union-Wade (born October 29, 1972)[1] is an American actor. She began her career in 1990s, appearing on television sitcoms, before landing supporting roles in teen comedy films She's All That and 10 Things I Hate About You (1999). Her breakthrough role was in the 2000 teen comedy film Bring It On, after which she was female lead in the short-lived CBS medical drama series City of Angels later that year.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt2072233</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Ryan Reynolds</name>
        <birthday>1976-10-23</birthday>
        <age>41</age>
        <biography>Ryan Rodney Reynolds (born October 23, 1976) is a Canadian actor. He portrayed Michael Bergen on the ABC sitcom Two Guys and a Girl (1998–2001), Billy Simpson in the YTV Canadian teen soap opera Hillside (1991), as well as Marvel Comics characters Hannibal King in Blade: Trinity (2004), Wade Wilson / Weapon XI in X-Men Origins: Wolverine (2009), and the title character in Deadpool (2016) for which he received a Golden Globe Award nomination.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1431045</movie>
            <movie>tt5442430</movie>
            <movie>tt5463162</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Michael Cera</name>
        <birthday>1988-06-07</birthday>
        <age>29</age>
        <biography>Michael Austin Cera (/ˈsɛrə/; born June 7, 1988)[1] is a Canadian actor and musician. He started his career as a child actor, most notably portraying a young Chuck Barris in Confessions of a Dangerous Mind (2002). He is mostly known for his role as George Michael Bluth on the sitcom Arrested Development and for his leading roles in the comedy films Superbad (2007), Juno (2007), Nick and Norah's Infinite Playlist (2008) and Youth in Revolt (2010). In 2010, he portrayed Scott Pilgrim in Scott Pilgrim vs. the World and played an exaggerated version of himself in This Is the End (2013). Cera made his Broadway debut in the 2014 installment of Kenneth Lonergan's This Is Our Youth.</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4116284</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Duan Sanderson</name>
        <birthday></birthday>
        <age></age>
        <biography></biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt4975722</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
    <actor>
        <name>Hermione Corfield</name>
        <birthday>1993-12-19</birthday>
        <age>24</age>
        <biography>Hermione Isla Conyngham Corfield[1] (born December 19, 1993) is an English actress. She has appeared in such movies as Mission: Impossible – Rogue Nation (2015), Mr. Holmes (2015), Pride and Prejudice and Zombies (2016), xXx: Return of Xander Cage (2017) and the upcoming King Arthur: Legend of the Sword (2017).</biography>
        <movies>
            <movie>tt1972591</movie>
        </movies>
    </actor>
</actors>